视频字幕由 SSK字幕组 制作发布
字幕只供学习 请勿做任何商业行为
敬请关注新浪微博@SSK字幕组
制作人、导演、编剧、主演：塞思·麦克法兰（《泰迪熊》导演，第85届奥斯卡主持人）
主演：查理兹·塞隆
死在西部的一百万种方式
亚利桑那州  1882
翻译：香蕉奶昔   校对：香蕉奶昔 Bezero
有些人 生错了时间 生错了地点
Some people are born into the wrong time and place.
这是1882年美国的西部边疆
This was the american frontier in 1882.
贫瘠的大陆 艰苦的生活
A hard land for hard folk.
时轴：络睿  压制：beloved  总监：Bezreo
粮食短缺
Food was scarce,
疾病肆虐
disease was rampant,
每一天 人们都在为生存而挣扎
and life was a daily struggle for survival.
见鬼 这位是1880年的美国小姐选美冠军
Hell, this was miss america in 1880.
屎都要被吓出来了
Holy shit.
要在如此严酷无情的国度里
To build a home and a life in
老树桩镇
始建于1856年
建立家庭 维系生机
this harsh, unforgiving country,
需要一个人英勇无畏 坚如钢铁
required that a man be bold, fearless, and tough as iron.
勇敢坚韧的人
The men who were courageous and resilient
才能在这里发达成功
were the men who prospered.
但总有些人 偏偏就是那种大大大脓包
But some men were just big, giant pussies.
看啊 看啊
Well, well.
你竟然出现了 斯塔克
Surprised you showed up, Stark.
好吧 你说如果我不来的话
Yeah, well, you said you would kill my family
就要杀我全家 烧我房子 所以
and burn my house down if I didn't, so...
拔枪
Draw.
我到底要说些什么才好
Is there anything at all that I can say
才能让你取消这场决斗
to get you to call this off?
难道你是黄种人吗 斯塔克
You yellow, Stark?
好吧 你这话
Oh, okay, well, that's a little
对我们这些来自遥远东方的勤劳的朋友们
racist to our hard working friends
有那么一点点种族歧视吧 对不对啊 伙计们
over here from the far east, right, guys?
拔枪啊 你个狗娘养的
Draw, you son of a bitch!
听着 我只是觉得 我们能否好好商量商量
Look, I just feel like if we can talk this out, you know.
我们可以商量出一个冷静理智的解决方案
We can find a calm, rational solution,
也许有一天 我们甚至还能对此一笑而过
and maybe we even laugh about it one day.
我没有心情笑 斯塔克
I ain't in the mood to laugh, Stark!
听着 幽默无所不在的
Look, there's always humor in any...
哦 对啦 这样你一定会笑
Oh, hey, look, this will make
看咱俩的影子
you laugh. Look at our shadows.
看起来咱俩的影子要亲嘴儿了
It looks like our shadows are about to kiss each other.
看看
Look at that.
等等 看这个 哦我天 查理 哦买噶
Oh, wait, watch this. Oh, my God, Charlie. Oh, my God.
谢谢啊 你太大方了
Thank you! This is so generous of you.
哦 哇呜 这
Oh, wow! This is...
你太棒了吧
What a terrific guy you are.
我们还不熟呢 但是 嘿
We barely know each other, but, hey,
感觉对了挡也挡不住 是吧 哈
when it's right, it's right, huh?
等我爽完了
I'll give you a little tap on the
我就拍拍你的帽子告诉你 好咓
hat when I'm good to go, OK?
看看 大家都笑了 是吧 我们都笑了
Look, we're laughing, right? We're laughing now.
我们到底在吵些什么
What were we even fighting about?
反正我忘了 你还记得么
I can't remember, can you?
你该死的羊 啃了我牧场里一半的草 斯塔克
Your Goddamn sheep grazed up half my ranch, Stark.
那些草再也长不回来了
That grass ain't never gonna grow back!
好吧 听着 这样行不行
All right, look, how about this?
我会补偿你的损失 好咓
I'll pay you the money you lost, okay?
只要给我两天时间
Just give me two days to sell off
我卖掉几头羊 把钱赔给你
a few of my sheep and i'll get you the money.
好咓 就两天
All right. Just two days.
如果拿不到钱 我就来找你
If I don't have that cash, I'm coming after ya.
好的 太棒了 谢谢你的耐心
Okay, great. Thank you so much for your patience.
真的非常感谢
I really appreciate it.
还有这些乡亲们
And what a relief for all these people
大老远跑来 希望我们和平解决
who came out here hoping that we would
他们也能松口气了
find an amicable solution to this, huh?
噢 你们谁先开枪啊
Aw, somebody shoot some fucker!
我请了半天假来看热闹的啊
I took a half-day off work for this!
好吧 我必须指出
Okay, I just want to point out
这家伙是我们学校里的英语老师
that guy's an english teacher at our school.
让你先尝点厉害
Just a little taste.
我是说 本来还挺好的 是吧
I mean, that should have been the end of it, right?
我是说 我说了会赔给他钱
I mean, I tell him I'll pay him off.
我们各走各的 就这样么好了
We go our separate ways, and that's it.
但他偏不 非要开枪打我的腿
But, no, he shoots me in the fucking leg.
我是说 也就啃了点草 可是拜托啊 看看这伤口
I mean, it's just a graze, but come on, look at that.
咋了
What?
你应该跟他决斗的
You should have fought him.
我应该跟他决斗
I should have fought him?
你说真的吗
You're serious.
路易丝 天啊 那个家伙是这儿的神枪手
Louise! My God! The guy is one of the best shots around.
我在他旁边
I look like I have parkinson's
-就好像的了帕金森综合症一样 -那是什么
- next to him. - What is that?
那就是上帝对我们表达的
It's just another way God
另一种神秘的爱
mysteriously shows that he loves us.
但你想 和那家伙决斗 就等于自杀
But, look, it would have been suicide to fight that guy.
阿尔伯特 我要和你分手
Albert, I'm breaking up with you.
啥
What?
是的 对不起
Yeah. I'm sorry.
我今天中枪了
I got shot today.
我知道
I know.
等等等等 等一下子
Wait, wait, wait. Hang on a sec.
路易丝 这到底从何说起
Louise, where is this coming from?
是因为刚那场决斗吗
Is this because of the gunfight?
不是 其实我很久以前就有这种感觉了
No, I've actually been feeling this way for a while.
你人很好 我只是
You're a great guy. I just...
我发现
I realized that
我想要的是别的东西
I want something else.
别的东西 路易丝 咱俩处了一年半了都
Something else? Louise, it's been a year and a half!
听着 我知道我只是个放羊的
Look, I know I'm just a sheep farmer,
但我存了
but I'm savi
是啊 可你连羊都放不好 阿尔伯特
Yeah, but you're not even a good sheep farmer, Albert.
你把羊放得到处都是
Your sheep are everywhere.
放羊唯一要做的
The one thing a sheep farmer has to do
就是把羊赶到一起 对吧
is keep all of his sheep in one place, all right.
那天我去你的农场
I went to your farm the other day,
我看到后院有一只羊
And I saw one in the backyard,
山上放着三只
three way up on the ridge,
池塘里游着两只 屋顶上还站着一只
two in the pond, and one on the roof.
屋顶上那头是布里吉特 好咓
Okay, that's Bridget, all right?
它就是点迟钝有点痴呆 可它十分地有爱
She has a problem with retardation, but she's full of love.
可这些都不重要 好吗
Look, we're getting off track here, all right?
你为啥不直接告诉我 问题在哪儿
Why don't you just tell me what the problem is?
然后也许我能处理好
And then maybe I can fix it?
也许我年纪再大一点
Maybe if I were older,
时间就恰恰好
the timing would be right.
可是如今人们都可以活到35岁了
But people are living to be 35 these days
一个姑娘并不是非得
and a girl doesn't have to just go off
急着把自己嫁掉了
and get married right away.
我只是想
I just, I have to...
我要做一回真正的自己
I have to work on myself.
哦买噶
Oh, my God.
-你还真那么说了 -什么
- You did not just say that. - What?
我要做一回真正的自己
"I have to work on myself."
路易丝 这是书里面老掉牙的台词了
Louise, that's the oldest line in the book.
你知道吗
You realize that.
不过没有关系
You know what, it's okay, though.
没事的 我知道你为什么这么说
It's all right. I know why you're saying it.
因为你不想跟我说 问题出在我身上
It's because you don't want to tell me that I'm the problem.
再见 阿尔伯特
Goodbye, Albert.
等等 路易丝 路易丝
Goodbye? Wait. Louise. Louise!
我爱你啊
I love you.
对不起
I'm sorry.
酒吧
爽啊 来啊 来啊
Yeah! Oh, come on, come on!
爽 爽 爽
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
你喜欢我日你吗 有木有
You like me fucking you, don't you?
喜欢 棒死了
I do. It's really terrific.
-好 噢 啊 爽 -哦
- Yeah! Oh! Ah! Yeah! - Oh...
啊
Ah...
嗨 爱德华
Hi, Edward.
嗨 米莉
Hi, Millie.
你在等露斯吗
You waiting for Ruth?
是啊 我提早下班了
Yeah, I got off work early, so I
所以我想带她去野餐
thought I'd take her out for picnic.
听起来她楼上也快完事儿了
It sounds like she's just about done up there.
用你那脏脏的牛仔乳液 射我一脸吧
Shoot that dirty cowboy cum all over my face!
我看上去还行吧
Do I look okay?
是是 你看起来不错
Yeah, you look good.
-不错的 -那就好
- You look good. - Oh, good.
内什么 爱德华 介意我问你个问题吗
Say, Edward, do you mind if I ask you something?
呃 当然
Uh, yeah, sure.
你不介意你女朋友
You're okay with your girlfriend
每天都要和十五个不同的男人嘿咻
screwing like 15 differnt guys everyday
并且靠这个赚钱吗
and getting paid to do it?
好吧 我的工作也很烂
Well, my job sucks, too.
我知道 但你毕竟是位补鞋匠呀
I know. But, I mean, you repair shoes.
爱迪
Eddie!
嗨 亲爱的
Oh, hi, sweetie.
你在这儿干什么
What are you doing here?
那个 我提早下班了
Well, I got off work early.
我想我们可以去小溪边散散步
And I thought we could go for a walk by the stream.
-哦 -哦
- oh. - oh...
你的口气 额
Oh, your breath is, uh...
哦 哦
Ooh! ooh.
-非得给他口交 对不起 -没关系
- I had to give a blowjob. Sorry. - Oh, that's okay.
没事儿 这束花送给你
It's okay. Here, I got you some flowers.
-好漂亮啊 -是啊 我们走吧
- They're beautiful! - Yeah, come on.
我男朋友是不是最棒的 米莉
Don't I have the best boyfriend, Millie?
老实讲 尼玛我也说不上来
Honestly, I have no fucking idea.
拜拜
Bye!
对了 露斯 克莱德·霍奇金斯
Oh, hey, Ruthie, Clyde Hodgkins
一会儿要过来
wanted to come by a little later on.
他想要什么服务
What did he want?
我觉得他想要爆菊
I think he wants anal.
亲爱的 我们有钱买那条
Oh, honey, we can afford to get
去教堂用的腰带了
you that new belt for church.
哦 那太棒了
Oh, that would be great!
就是说嘛
I know!
那我五点半送她回来 行吗
So like 5:30? Does that work?
啊 应该可以
Ah, that should work. Yeah.
好吧 他预约了几点
Well, what time is his appointment?
额 这儿可不是牙科医院 爱德华
Uh, it's really not like a dentist's office here, Edward.
你懂的 他什么时候想把鸡鸡插别人菊花
You know, he'll just come by
他就会过来了
when he feels like putting his penis inside an asshole.
好 那就五点半好了
Yes, we'll just say 5:30.
好
Okay.
又上去了
Oh, shit.
你迟到了
You're late.
迟到什么了
For what?
好吧有道理
Fair enough.
阿尔伯特
Albert.
嘿 伙计们
Hey, guys.
你和路易丝的事儿 我们听说了
We heard about Louise.
太糟糕了
That's horrible.
我们很遗憾 阿尔伯特
We're so sorry, Albert.
你们想坐坐吗
Do you want to sit down?
我不用了 我想歇一歇菊花
I'm good. I'm gonna rest my asshole.
我在看我和路易丝的老照片
I was just looking at these old pictures of me and Louise.
这张是狂欢节拍的
This is from the carnival.
是哦
Oh, yeah.
这张是小镇野餐的时候拍的
There's the town picnic.
哦
Oh.
这是跳方块舞的时候拍的
This is the square dance.
我真的好希望 我们在照片里能笑一笑
I almost wish you could smile in photographs.
路易丝的笑容真的好迷人
Louise has such an amazing smile.
-那会感觉怪怪的 -哈
- That'd be weird. - huh?
你在照片里笑过吗
Have you ever smiled in a photograph?
-从没 你呢 -当然没有
- No, have you? - Oh, God, no.
如果笑的话 你会像个神经病
No, you'd look like an insane person.
你知道吗 我坐在这儿一直想
But, it's just, you know, I've been sitting here
尼玛为什么
trying to figure out how the hell
我竟然把事儿搞砸了
I could have screwed this up.
我做什么都是为了她
I did everything for her.
只要她高兴 我就开心
If she was happy, I was happy.
我只在乎她
That's all I cared about.
有她在 那些什么枪啊炮啊
And she was the one thing that made the shootings,
疾病啊 猛兽啊 印第安人啊
and the diseases, and the wild animals, and the indians,
还有在西部的各种破事儿啊
and the general depressing awfulness about the west
全都能忍了
bearable.
天啊 我好爱她
God, I love her so much.
你说得我都要哭了
You're gonna make me cry.
-我们去喝个烂醉 -好
- Let's get fucked up. - Yeah.
那 你现在要怎么办
So, what are you gonna do?
呃
Uh...
我也不知道该怎么办
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
玩玩自杀吧 也许
Commit suicide, maybe.
阿尔伯特 我知道现在你心如死灰
Albert, I know everything seems hopeless right now.
但我保证 活下去的理由还有好多
But I promise you, there's so much to live for.
真的吗 有吗
Really? Is there?
1882年的西部边疆 有什么活下去的理由
What is there to live for on the frontier in 1882? Huh?
听我给你们说
Look, let me tell you something.
我们生活在一个恐怖的地区和时代
We live in a terrible place and time.
美国西部简直是个恶心的
The American west is a disgusting,
可怕的 肮脏的 危险的地方
awful, dirty, dangerous place ! Look at that.
你看看周围
Look around you.
除了你自己 什么都能让你翘辫子
Everything out here that's not you wants to kill you.
亡命之徒 暴怒酒鬼
Outlaws, angry drunk people,
淫荡妓女 饥饿野兽
scorned hookers,hungry animals,
疾病伤痛 印第安人 天气气候
diseases, major and minor injuries, indians, the weather.
你连去个澡堂子都会被杀
You can get killed just going to the bathroom.
我每次去个茅房
I take my life in my hands every
都觉得危在旦夕
time I walk out to my outhouse!
因为外面草地上到处都是响尾蛇
There's fucking rattlesnakes all in the grass out there.
即使我活下来了 你知道还有啥会要我命吗
And even if I make it, you know what can kill me?
霍乱 你知道霍乱吧
Cholera. You know cholera?
-黑色瘟疫 -黑色瘟疫
- The black shit. - The black shit.
西部疾病俱乐部
The latest offering in the frontier's
每个月的压轴好戏
disease-of-the-month club.
然后 即使你这样都还没死
And even if you survive all those things,
你们知道还有什么要你命么
you know what else can kill you?
该死的医生 连医生都会要你命
The fucking doctor. The doctor can kill you.
前些年我感冒了 我到医院
I had a cold a couple of years ago. I went in there.
你猜医生对我说啥 他说
You know what he said to me? He goes,
你要去弄个耳钉戴戴
"Oh, you need an ear nail."
尼玛 要在我耳朵上钉个钉子
A nail in my fucking ear.
那是最新的药 能治好你的病
That is modern medicine for you.
可是医生 我高烧39度
"Yeah, doc, I have a fever of 102."
哦 你需要给驴子踢上两脚
"Oh, you need a donkey kickin'."
我们的牧师开枪杀了两个人 牧师啊
You know our pastor has shot two people? Our pastor.
-不可能 不会的 -不是吧
- No, no. - No.
对上帝发誓 他决斗中射杀了个家伙
Honest to God. Shot a guy in a duel
然后又回去杀了那家伙年幼的儿子
and then went back and killed the guy's teenage son
因为他担心这儿子会来报仇
because he was afraid he would kill him out of revenge.
等等 你怎么知道的
Wait, how do you know that?
他竟然在布道的时候跟我们讲这个
Because he did a whole fucking sermon about it!
讲了一堂课的要看开 要想开
A lesson about seeing things through.
顺便说句 看到那边那群家伙了吗
By the way, look at this. See those guys over there?
他们是银矿的矿工
The guys who work in the silver
看到他们在吃什么吗
mines? See what they are eating?
排骨蘸辣酱
Ribs doused in hot sauce.
他们餐餐都要吃辣
They eat hot spicy foods every meal of the day.
知道为啥吗
You know why?
因为他们在银矿下面
Because their palates are so completely fucking dulled
每天要吸12个小时的毒气
from inhaling poisoned gas, 12
味觉已经快完全丧失了
hours a day, down under the mine!
他们只能尝出辣味儿
That's all they can taste.
你知道整天吃这种东西 对你肠胃多大害处吗
You know what that kind of diet does to your guts?
便秘 肠胃抽搐 消化不良 肝病
Constipation, cramps, dyspepsia, liver disease,
肾病 痔疮 肠炎
kidney disease, hemorrhoids, bowel inflammation.
他们放个屁都能毒死自己
They literally die from their own farts.
还有 你还想看更多的死亡事件吗
And, oh, oh, you want to see more death?
我们只要站起来走出大门
All we got to do is get up and walk out the front door.
那个是我们的市长
That is our mayor.
他死翘翘了
He is dead.
他死在那里 已经整整三天了
He has been lying there, dead, for three days.
根本没人去鸟他
No one has done a thing.
没人去碰他 没人去调查死因
Not moved him, not looked into his death,
甚至没有暂时推选个代市长
Not even replaced him with a temporary appointee.
过去整整三天里
For the last three days, the
我们镇的最高行政长官
highest-ranking official in our town
竟然是个死人
has been a dead guy.
哦 看啊 看啊
Oh! Look at that! Look at that!
饿狼来叼走尸体了
Wolves are dragging the body away
赤裸裸地给我提供论据啊
as if to illustrate my point.
永别了 市长先生
Bye! Bye, Mr. mayor!
就要变成狼屎了 要开心呀 永别了
Bye! Have fun becoming wolf shit! Bye!
上苍啊
God!
这 我的朋友们 就是美国的西部
That, my friends, is the american west.
一个恶心的 可怕的 肮脏的 绝望的粪坑
A disgusting, awful, dirty cesspool
都见鬼去吧
of despair, and  fuck all of it.
给我闭嘴你
Why don't you shut up?
你才闭嘴呢
You shut up!
呜 呜
Mmm, mmm...
嗷 露斯 疼
Ow! Ruth. Jesus Christ.
-别这样 -好吧好吧
- Stop it. - Okay, fine.
至少明天去哈珀医生那儿看看吧
At least have Dr. Harper take a look at it tomorrow.
你听听自己的话吧
If you could hear yourself right now.
你知道的我去了哈珀先生 会怎么样吗
You know what's gonna happen if I go to Dr. Harper
我跟他说 看看我的伤口吧
And I say, "Take a look at that"?
他会说 噢 看起来很疼的样子
He's gonna say, "Oh, that looks like it hurts.
我去找只蓝松鸦来 帮你把血啄干净
"Let me give you a blue jay to peck out the blood."
或许你应该
Maybe you should...
我不知道 或许你应该去和路易丝谈谈
I don't know, maybe you should try to talk to Louise.
-那倒是个好主意 -是吧
- That's a great idea. - Yeah?
-醍醐灌顶啊 -哈
- That's the jackpot. That's the jackpot! - Huh?
-我还可以的吧 -好
- I still got it! - Okay.
我偶尔还是能出出主意的
I have good ideas sometimes.
我说的不是现在
I didn't mean now!
嘿 哥们儿 酒驾是违法的呀
Hey, hey, dude, you really shouldn't drink and horse.
不要不要 别别
No. No. No. No. No. No.
好好地去吧 好吧
Yeah, there you... Okay.
好了 柯蒂斯 伙计
Okay, Curtis. Curtis, buddy,
我马上就回来 好吗
I'm gonna be right back. I'll be right back, okay?
或者在里面过个夜
Or not!
好吧 这要求有点过分
No, that's being too ambitious.
嘿 嘿
Hey. Hey.
阿尔伯特 你搞什么鬼
Albert, what the hell are you doing?
路易丝 我们要谈谈
Louise, we need to talk.
-现在是凌晨一点半 -我们要谈谈
It's like 1:30 in the morning. - We need to talk.
-我们今晚就得谈谈 -你的脸怎么了
- And we need to talk tonight. - What happened to your face?
我和一头无名野兽练了练拳脚
I got in a fight with an animal that I could not identify.
好吧 你醉了
Okay, you're drunk.
我只有一丁点儿醉
I'm a smucks-dinnin' drunk.
我不知道你想干啥 可现在太晚了
I don't know what you want from me, but it's late.
-我要关门了 -路易丝 路易丝
- I gotta go. - Louise! Louise!
路易丝求求你 听我说 我爱你
Louise, please, listen to me. I love you, okay?
我爱你
I love you.
我只是觉得 我们要是能谈一谈心
And I just think if we talked this out
我们就可以把问题解决了
that we can get somewhere and fix it.
听着阿尔伯特 你该走了
Look, Albert, you gotta go.
你会找到另一半的 但绝不是我
I'm sure you're right for somebody else, just not for me.
好吗
Okay?
晚安
Good night.
等等 让我抚摸一下你
Wait, let me just touch you.
你真是个混蛋
You're being a fucking jerk!
好吧 我明天再来找你
Okay, I'll talk to you tomorrow.
你知道吗 有次我听到你放屁了
You know what? I heard you fart once.
就是这种声音
And it went...
非常悦耳
And it was a sharp one.
悦耳中还带点屎
A little sharpie poop-toot.
我还听到
And I heard...
你知道我会用这块金子买啥吗
You know what I'm gonna get with this gold coming?
你猜我会给你买啥
You know what I'm gonna get you?
我要给你买上一大堆新鲜的排骨
I'm gonna get you a big old stack of fresh-cut steaks.
我打赌你一定喜欢
I bet you'd like that.
怎么了
What? What's the matter with...
安静 小家伙
Settle down, boy.
拜托小家伙 别吵了普拉格
Come on, boy, hey! Quiet down, Plugger!
哇哦 吁
Whoa, mule!
好啊 朋友们
Howdy, folks.
好啊
Howdy.
需要我帮忙吗 伙计们
What can I do for you fellas?
我们想穿过谢尔曼湾
Well, we're riding through to Sherman Creek.
不知道有没有捷径 谢谢
Be obliged if you could tell us the shortest route.
好的 我可以帮上忙
Oh, yeah, I can help you with that.
我这儿有张地图
I got a map right here.
是的先生
Yes, sir.
哦
Oh.
你们现在在大路上
You're on the main road now.
这条大路正好穿过牛头山
And the main road goes right through Bullhead
通往谢尔曼湾
and straight through to Sherman Creek.
不过你想找捷径
But if you want the quickest way,
我建议走比尔比关口
I'd take bilbee pass.
也更安全 更不容易遇到土匪
Safer, too. Less chance of bandits and such.
谢谢
Thank you.
-送给你啦 -哦
- You can keep that. - Oh.
呃 还有件事可能需要你帮忙
Uh, one more thing you might do for us.
啥事儿
What's that?
把你的金子给我们看看
You could show us the gold.
金子
Gold?
我没有金子啊
I ain't got no gold.
我倒是想
I wish.
在上头苦苦淘了好久呢 可是
Been prospecting up there, but
那条溪流里的金子几乎被淘完了
that stream's about panned out.
老狗普拉格和我已经放弃了
Old plugger and I done give it up.
我们正要回镇上去呢
We're going on back into town.
好吧 我想情况应该是这样的
Aye. you see, that's... that's just it.
正午时分 你往镇上赶
You're heading back to town in the middle of the day.
淘金者只有淘到金子 想拿回去卖了 才会这样
A prospector only does that when he's found gold to sell.
把金子给我
Show it to me.
我发誓 先生
No, I swear to you, mister.
我没有什么金子
I ain't got no gold.
我们只是回镇上去找点儿
We're just going into town to get some...
哇哦 哇哦 哇哦
Whoa, whoa, whoa...
-慢着 让我想想再 -好好想
- Hold on, let me think here a minute. - You do that.
我可能有那么一丁点儿小金子
I might just have a little bit of gold.
找到啦 我给忘了
Yeah, here it is. I forgot all about it.
拿去吧
Here, take it.
拔枪
Pick up your gun.
什么
What?
我不会无缘无故拿走你的金子 那叫偷窃
Well, I'm not just gonna take your gold. That'd be stealing.
你知道么 老前辈 我们来决斗
You know what, old timer? We'll shoot for it.
-柯林奇 -闭嘴
- Clinch. - Shut up.
金子你尽管拿去好了
You just take the gold, okay?
只有小偷才这么做
Only a thief would do that.
你会叫我小偷吗 老前辈
Are you calling me a thief, old timer?
不会不会
No, no, no!
那就拔枪
Then pick up your gun.
很好
That's it.
瞄准我
Now point it at me.
数到三 一起开枪
We shoot on three.
一
One.
二
Two.
该死的 柯林奇
God damn it, Clinch!
他又不是非死不可
You didn't have to shoot him!
我知道不是非死不可 亲爱的
I know I didn't have to, sweetheart.
他本来就要给你金子了
He would've given you the gold!
关键是 我还得问他要两次
The point is I had to ask him twice.
我很忙的 时间宝贵
I'm a busy man with a schedule.
狗娘养的说的就是你
You're a son of a bitch is what you are.
以后不准你在我手下面前说这种话
Don't you ever say that to me in front of my men.
老婆要敬爱老公
A man's wife will respect him.
好了 再说一遍
Now, let's try that again.
我的上帝呀 我爱你
Oh, my God, I love you.
我简直是天底下 以及历史上 最幸福的老婆
I'm, like, the luckiest girl ever in the history of girls.
就要这样 上马吧
That's it. Now, mount up.
嘿 柯林奇
Hey, Clinch.
看看这个
Take a look.
穿过牛头山要花一天半
You'd lose half a day going through Bullhead.
你 伊诺克 乔迪 跟我走
You, Enoch and Jordy will ride with me.
我们走比尔比关口 取谢尔曼湾捷径
We'll take Bilbee pass to Sherman Creek trail.
我们干下这一票之后
And make no mistake about the
会有人穷追不舍的
kind of heat we're gonna draw
到时可不能麻痹大意
after we take that stage.
安娜 你就不跟我们去冒险了
Anna, I'm gonna keep you out of harm's way.
刘易斯 你带着安娜朝东走
Lewis, you take Anna and ride east
在老树桩镇等我们
And hole up here in, uh, Old Stump.
老树桩镇
都明白了吧
You got that?
等我们把事儿办完
We'll let things cool
十二天后来接你们
for a wee bit and then we'll come for you in 12 days.
过来 乖乖
Come on, boy.
过来 普拉格 真棒
Come on, Plugger. Come on! yeah!
好小子 我们走
Good boy! Let's go!
噢 不是吧
Oh, Jesus Christ!
看看谁睡到下午两点才起
Well, look who's up at 2:00 in the afternoon.
桌上还有一点猪屁股肉
There's still some pig ass and
还有一点甜酪 如果你饿的话
sweet cream there if you want them
我要去下茅房 呃
I'm gonna use the outhouse. um...
如果我在外面挂了 能帮我个忙吗
If I die out there, will you guys just do me one favor?
一次就好 我想看你们换位置坐坐
Just once, I want you to switch seats.
滚开
Fuck off.
好吧
Okay.
哦
Oh.
爱德华 嗨 怎么了
Ah, Edward, hey. What's going on?
天呐阿尔伯特 你看起来糟透了
Oh, my God. Albert, you look terrible!
哇哦 正需要有人给我打打气
Oh, wow, there's that confidence boost I need.
谢谢啊 你怎么样兄弟
Thanks a lot. How you doing, buddy?
好吧 说实话我有点担心
Well, honestly, I'm a little worried about you.
这一个半星期 都没看到你去镇上了
I haven't seen you in town in a week and a half
还有 你看起来貌似
And, you know, it seems like you're
整天宅家里睡大觉
just staying in and sleeping all day
我可没有整天宅家里 我有出去过的
No, I don't stay home all day. I go out.
你知道星期二我做了啥吗
You know what I did on tuesday?
我去了查理·布兰奇的牧场
I went out to Charlie Blanche's ranch
还了他的钱
And I paid him the money I owe him.
免得他拿枪嘣我脑瓜
So he won't shoot me in the fucking face.
也算是出门了吧
I did that. That's going out.
好吧 我可不是指这种出门
Well, that's not really what I'm talking about.
好吧听着 那我说真心话吧
Okay, look. Here's the truth, all right?
我觉得要在家里多陪陪父母
I just feel like I need to stay here with my parents.
和他们在一起 一天少一天
They're not gonna be around much longer
我只是想回报
And I just want to be able to give
我一路走来
back all the love and affection
他们给予我的爱和关怀
that I got growing up.
是吧伙计们
You know? Right, guys?
嗷
Ow!
你又屁里带针了吧 老爸
Oh, you getting the fart needles again, dad?
我屁里带什么不用你管
Never mind what I'm getting!
我好爱他哦
I love him so much!
阿尔伯特 我知道分手
Albert, I know you're taking this
让你痛不欲生
breakup really hard
可你总归要走出来
But you got to get out of this funk.
你看你都N个星期没剪羊毛了
I mean, you haven't shorn your sheep in weeks.
听着 你没经历过不知道
Look, you don't know what this is like, all right.
恕我直言 尼玛你一点点都
With all due respect, you have no
不懂我有多痛苦 好咓啦
fucking clue with what this is like?
你每天晚上都可以
All right? You're going home every night
和爱你的女朋友一起回家
to your girlfriend who loves you.
-你们一起滚床单 你们还 -啊
- You're having sex with her, and you... - Ah...
没啦 露斯和我还 还没有做过那事儿
No, Ruth and I have... we've never done that.
还没有 是什么意思
What do you mean you've...
你还没和露斯嘿咻过
You've never had sex with Ruth?
还没有 没有
Yeah. no, no. Yeah.
慢着 她在妓院不是每天都要和
Wait, doesn't she have sex with, like,
差不多十来个家伙嘿咻吗
10 guys every day at the whore house?
是啊 那还算少的
On a slow day, yeah.
可你们俩还没嘿咻过
But you guys have never had sex?
没有没有 露斯想等到我们结婚了再嘿咻
No. no, Ruth wants to wait until we get married.
她是基督徒 我也是
You know, she's a Christian and so am I,
我们想把第一次留到新婚之夜
And we want to save ourselves for our wedding night.
爱德华 你和别人嘿咻过吗
Edward, have you... have you ever had sex with anyone?
和我的叔叔倒是有过一次不明不白的 不过那个
Well, there was some shit with my uncle, but that was...
整个过程已经记不太清了
You know, it's really hard to remember all that stuff.
那什么 你说得对
You know, yeah, you're right.
我这样下去可能会更惨
Things could be a lot worse.
对
Yeah.
我会出门见人的 谢谢你
Um, I'll get out, I'll meet some people. Yeah, thanks.
好的
Okay.
嗷 这个屁从我鸡鸡里出来了
Ow! That came out of my penis!
最近到处都能看到 小孩儿都在滚铁圈儿
Man, I see kids everywhere with those stick hoops lately.
我也是
I know. Me, too.
这种游戏对大脑发育没啥好处 是吧
It's got to be bad for their brains, right?
是啊 会导致他们注意力涣散
Yeah, it stunts their attention span.
我从报纸上读到的
I read an article in the paper.
我也看到了 他们整天盯着铁圈儿
Yeah, I saw that. it's like they lose the power to innovate.
会让他们失去创新能力
Because they're staring at the stick hoop all day.
对
Yep.
哦对了 他们今天要把
Oh, by the way, they're delivering
镇上的冰块运过来
the town's ice shipment today.
想去看热闹吗
You want to go watch?
-好啊 一定很有意思 -对
- Oh, yeah, that'd be fun. - Yeah!
把这么多的冰块运到同一个地方
Yeah. It's always a thrill when you get to see
一定看起来很牛逼
that much ice all in one place.
我也觉得 好激动啊
Yeah, I think so, too. I'm really excited.
爱德华 快看 快看
Edward, Edward, look, look.
我去年买了表的
Holy shit.
是那个该死的弗依
Fucking Foy.
她还跟我说 不想谈恋爱了
She told me she didn't want to see anybody.
她还说 想好好做一回自己
She told me she had to work on herself.
你看看她
Look at that.
哦买噶 该死的弗依
Oh, my God. Fucking Foy!
他是那个胡须用品店的老板
The owner of the moustachery.
看看看看 他竟然在亲她
Oh, look at that. He's kissing her.
-还舌吻 -该死的弗依
- He's frenching her. - Fucking Foy!
也许你也该留个胡子
Maybe you should grow a moustache.
我可留不起
No, I can't afford it.
胡须乳液 胡须蜡 胡须清洁液
The creams, the waxes, the lotions.
我没那么多钱买
I don't have the money.
该死的弗依
Fucking Foy!
阿尔伯特 或许我们应该去一下教堂
Hey, Albert, maybe we should just go to church.
在那里你会感觉舒畅一点
It'll make you feel a lot better.
去教堂也没用
Church is not gonna...
哦嘿 看 是冰块
Oh, hey, look! It's the ice!
文迪斯&索乌 冰工厂
为啥要这么大块
Why is it so big?
这样就不容易融化了
So it doesn't melt.
啊哦
Oh.
好洁白啊
That's so neat.
冰块的来历 其实也很有趣哦
I know. it's actually really interesting how they do it.
远在波士顿有个公司
It's this one company out in boston
专门从结冰的湖啊池塘啊里面
that basically cuts it in big blocks
切出大块大块的冰块上来
from frozen lakes and ponds, and
然后他们再把这些大冰块运往
they just ship all of the...
噢 噢
Oh! oh...
哦我了个天 哦我了个去
Oh, my God! oh, my God!
这种死法也太突然了吧
That went south so fast!
噢 噢
Oh! Oh!
别搞错了 我的孩子们
And make no mistake, my children.
对于所有的无产牧民
There shall be swift and righteous
我们应该采取果断而公正的制裁手段
justice on all free grazers.
坚决不容许他们
No more shall they nibble wantonly
继续蚕食我们的私人牧场
at the teat of our coffers.
这也符合圣经的那个章节中
And that's just exactly like that part in the Bible
所描述的类似情形
that applies to that situation.
（神棍牧师自己也不清楚哪个章节里说过...）
在此我还想对詹姆斯·埃迪森的家人
I would also like to offer a heartfelt prayer
致以真诚的慰问
to the family of James Addison,
詹姆斯·埃迪森今早在卸载冰块的时候
who was killed this morning
被冰块砸死了
while unloading the ice shipment.
詹姆斯 今年炎炎夏日 当我们啜饮着清凉饮料的时候
James, we will think of you lovingly this july
我们会想起你亲切的面容
as we sip the cold summer beverages
为了那一刻凉爽 你献出了生命
for which you gave your life.
这些人 竟然还打算用那块该死的冰块
They're still gonna use the fucking ice.
现在 在我们结束早祷告之前
Now, before we end this morning's service,
我想热烈欢迎我们镇的两位新成员
I would like to welcome two new members to our community.
刘易斯·巴恩斯 和他的妹妹 安娜
Lewis Barnes and his sister, Anna.
他们刚搬来我们老树桩镇
They've just moved here to Old Stump
他们打算在这儿建个农场
and they plan to build a farm.
让我们真心地祝他们好运
And we wish them all the luck.
好了 今天的祷告到此结束
Well, that concludes today's service.
接下来的一星期 愿上帝保佑着你们
So, may God bless you for another week.
还有 最近有一只山狮在镇上出没 大家小心
And there is a mountain lion warning in effect.
胡须用品店
洁须液
护须膏
胡须精油
嗨
Hi.
嘿 你来啦
Hey, you.
-赶集的日子到啦 -嗯
- So, the fair's coming up... - Mmm?
我在想我们待会可以去买几件衣服
And I was thinking that we could go dress shopping later.
我的确认为你该买件新礼服了
I was thinking you need a new dress.
买件贵的
Something expensive?
贵到爆的
Stupidly expensive!
好棒
Okay.
喔 我滴个神啊 哇哦
Oh, Jesus. Wow.
嗨 阿尔伯特
Hi, Albert.
哈罗
Hello.
咋类小子 从没见你来过这儿
What's up, kiddo? Never seen you in here before.
就瞎逛逛
Just browsing.
好吧
Yeah.
不过 你貌似没有胡子
You don't have a moustache, though.
我知道 我在考虑留个胡子
No, I know. I was thinking about growing one.
骚瑞 听不清
I'm sorry, I can't...
-我说我在考虑留个胡子 -噢
- I said I was thinking about growing one. - Oh.
不好意思 我去补个妆
Excuse me, I have to use the powder room.
你打算留什么样的胡子
And just what kind of moustache are you looking to grow?
呃 留个逼格的
Um, a big one.
要那种沿着我的嘴巴
Like one of those ones that goes down
这样子下来
along the side of my mouth,
然后沿着我的下巴上去
and then goes up the edge of my jaw,
然后融入我的两鬓
and then becomes my sideburns,
最后融入我的头发里
and then becomes my hair.
你是说 莫比乌斯胡
A Möbius moustache.
莫比乌斯胡 就是它
M?bius moustache, that's the one.
好吧 嗯
Yeah. Um...
你应该知道那种胡子
You should know that kind of moustache
是一样非常昂贵的面部装饰
is a very costly facial accessory.
是的 我知道
Yeah, I know that.
可你是个放羊的
Well, you're a sheep farmer.
我问你 你对你的所作所为
Let me ask you something. You feel
感觉良好吗
good about what you are doin'.
我究竟做了啥
What exactly am I doing?
抢了别人的妹子 这就是你的所作所为
Stealing a guy's girlfriend. That's what you're doing.
你感觉良好吗
You feel good about that?
嘿 是路易丝甩的你 我的朋友
Hey, Louise dumped you, my friend.
她想要一个有钱的男人 这又不是我的错
It's not my fault she wanted someone with more to offer.
我能给她一个奢华的家
I can give her a lavish home.
暖暖的毯子 大袋大袋的糖果
Warm blankets, wrapped candies.
你能做到吗 阿尔伯特
Can you say the same, Albert?
你能给路易丝 大袋大袋的糖果吗
Can you give Louise wrapped candies?
你造吗 日你啊
You know what? Fuck you, man.
对啊 她确实日了我
Yeah, that's what she's doing.
酒吧
哦嗨 亲爱的
Oh, hey, sweetie.
嗨
Hi!
-嗨 马科 -嘿 爱德
- Hi, Mark. - Hey, Ed.
哇哦 真是漫长的一天哦
Wow! What a long day!
噢 怎么啦
Oh, what happened?
好吧 比如有个男的
Oh, gosh! Well, like, this one
要我抽着雪茄
man wanted me to smoke cigar
然后一边给他吹 一边把烟灰弹到他的蛋蛋上
and then ash on his balls while I'm jerking him off.
然后我就想 啥 我能同时做这些动作吗
And I'm like, "what? can I do all that?"
好吧
Yeah.
内什么 露斯 我最近在想
You know, uh, Ruth, I've been thinking.
想啥
About what?
我爱你
Well, I love you.
我也爱你
Well, I love you, too.
我们在一起好久了
And we've been together for a long time.
你
Wh...
你觉得我们一起共度良宵怎么样
What do you think about us spending the night together?
你是说嘿咻
You mean having sex?
我们不一定要马上嘿咻啊
Maybe not right away, you know?
前面几次我们可以一起躺着啥都不做
We could maybe lie together for the first couple of times
看看感觉怎么样 然后再从长计议嘛
and see how it feels, and then go from there.
可是爱迪 我们是基督徒呀
But, Eddie, we're Christians.
我知道我们是基督徒
I know we're Christians.
而且我也想在上帝的注视下 做最正确的事儿
And I want to do the correct thing in the eyes of the lord.
可如果我们是真心相爱
But if we really do love each other,
你不觉得 上帝是会同意我们共度良宵的吗
Don't you think God would be okay with it?
我也不知道
I don't know.
我是说 这可是婚前性行为啊
I mean, you're talking about pre-marital relations.
喔 你的脸上有点脏东西 我来擦掉
Oh! You've got a little thing right here. I'll get it.
呀呀
Oops. Oopsie.
-谢谢你 -噢
- Thank you. - Oh.
决定了 我这就走
That's it, I'm out.
啥
What?
我受够了 我要远走高飞 去旧金山
I'm done. I'm leaving. I'm going to San Francisco.
你玩儿真的吗 就因为路易丝
What, are you serious? Because of Louise?
是 我玩儿真的 是 就因为路易丝
Yes, I'm serious. and, yes, it is because of Louise.
我竟然忍了这么久
I don't know how I lasted this long.
我讨厌西部边疆 我讨厌这儿的一切
I hate the frontier, I hate everything in it.
那我该咋办 我是你最好的朋友
Well, what am I gonna do? I'm your best friend.
我懂 所以我要你收下这个
I know. that's... that's why I want you to have these.
阿尔伯特 这是你最爱的一双袜子
Albert, these are your favorite socks.
对
Yeah.
那我要你收下这个
And I want you to have that.
爱德华 这是你的幸运小手帕
Edward, this is your lucky handkerchief.
对
Yeah.
啊黏黏的
It's sticky.
好啊 你也好啊
Well, hello to you, too!
詹姆斯 我找到有爱的本地人啦
James, I found the friendly locals.
然后他说 你干麻不去操你自己的马
So he said, "why don't you go blow your own horse?"
嘿 看着点儿 朋友
Hey, watch it, pal.
我觉着你欠我一杯酒啊 哥们儿
I think you owe me a drink, fella.
欠你个鬼
The hell I do.
你得看看这是谁的地盘
You best watch where you stand.
我想你没听清楚
I don't think you heard me.
我渴了
I'm thirsty.
那你干麻不滚去河里 喝个痛快
Then why don't you go on down the river and take a dunk?
最后一次机会 屁孩儿
Last chance, kid.
噢 糟糕
Oh, shit!
阿尔伯特 快 各就各位
Albert, hurry! Get in position!
我们要一决高下
We got our own thing going on over here.
对 谁都不许插手
Yeah, nobody needs to get in on this.
不缺个胳膊断个腿 决不罢休
We're both getting hurt pretty badly.
谁也别想来争
Nobody needs to come over here.
这里的战斗
This fight is way more violent than yours...
比你们那儿的惨烈多啦
All those other guys' fights.
嗷
Oh!
你还真的打我了
You actually hit me!
真对不起
I'm so sorry.
你个狗日的
You fucker!
我就加了点新动作
I put a new move in there.
你不能随便加新动作
You don't just put a new move in.
我们开会讨论过了啊
That's why we have the meetings.
就这里疼 就这里
That's where it hurts. Like, right there.
眼眶下面
Like, right underneath my eye.
是啊 有个小红块
Yeah, there's a little red spot.
嗷 小心你 这儿很娇嫩的
Ow! Careful, it's tender.
-谢谢你 -应该的
- Thank you. - Sure.
糟糕 快来
Shit. Come on.
哇哦
Whoa!
真不好意思
Sorry about that.
打架斗殴是这里常有的事儿
It's kind of a regular occurrence around here.
-真的么 -对
- Really? - Yeah.
嘿 刚那一手挺快的
Hey, pretty fast hands back there.
-喔 -你真是个大英雄呢
- Oh... - I guess you're a real hero.
我吗 我可不是英雄
Me? No, I'm not the hero.
我会躲在人堆里 取笑英雄穿的汗衫
I'm the guy in the crowd making fun of the hero's shirt.
-我就是这种人 -噢
- That's who I am. - Oh.
-嘿 快看谁来啦 -它是谁
- Hey, look who's here. - Who's this?
它叫普拉格
This is plugger.
嗨 普拉格
Hey, plugger.
那个 酒馆里面那位是你的哥哥
So, that... that was your brother in there, huh?
对 刘易斯 他总是那么缺根经
Yeah, Lewis. He's always been a little rambunctious.
好吧 还不错吧 对了 我叫阿尔伯特
Yeah, he seems like a great guy. I'm Albert, by the way.
我是安娜
Anna.
你们是刚到镇上来吗
You guys just got into town?
对
Yeah.
欢迎来到我们屌爆了的老树桩镇
Welcome to our awesome town.
多谢
Thanks.
刘易斯和我刚从堪萨斯城过来
Lewis and I just came out from Kansas city.
噢 堪萨斯州吗
Oh, Kansas.
是密苏里州的那个堪萨斯城
No, it's in missouri.
哦对 那个吵嚷嚷的怪城
Oh, right. that's annoying and weird.
我们想换换环境
We were wanting a change,
就来西部边疆建个农场看看
So we came out to the frontier looking to build a farm.
-我就是干这行的 -真的假的
- Oh, that's what I do. - Really?
真的 我的农场离这儿差不多两公里
Yeah, I got a farm about 2 miles from here.
养牛吗
Oh, cattle?
额不是 养羊的
Uh, no, sheep.
-喔 -对
- Oh. - Yep.
好吧 不过那可是一份充实的工作 对吧
Well, that's got to be fulfilling work, though, right?
啊 对的 很充实
Ah, yeah, it's great.
就像是在遛狗 每天要遛150多只蠢得要死的狗
It's like being a dog walker for 150 really stupid dogs.
-哦我擦 普拉格 -哦我去啊
- Oh, shit, plugger! - Oh, my God!
-普拉格 快给我 -天啊 这是神马
- Plugger, give it to me. - Jesus, what is that?
是市长的脚
It's the mayor.
哎哟我去
Oh, shit!
那你们俩是怎么认识的
So, how did you guys meet?
她几年前搬来镇上
Uh, she moved to town a couple years ago
到这边教书
to take over the schoolmarm job.
（风滚草：戈壁常见植物，干旱来临时会团成一团随风滚动。）
原来的那位女教师 被飞速滚动的风滚草
Our old schoolmarm got her throat
割断了喉咙
slit by a fast-moving tumbleweed.
-我的天呐 -嗯
- Oh, my God! - Yeah.
孩子们都目睹了吗
In front of the kids?
哦对 所有孩子都目睹了
Oh, yeah. yeah. All of them.
我来帮你
Let me help you.
看你卷着都很痛苦
That is just painful to watch.
你知道吗 我们在一起的全部时光里
And, you know, it's like the whole time we were together
我一直在想着
I just remember thinking,
我竟然可以如此快乐
"How can I possibly be this happy?
她现在是喜欢我
"She likes me now,
可总有一天 她会发现
"but one day, she is gonna figure out
我也许配不上她
"that she is too good for me."
然后终于有一天 她发现了
And then one day, she did.
我感觉我好不容易
I feel like I finally tricked one
把一个姑娘骗到手
girl into falling in love with me.
然后却又失去了她
And then I lost her.
我倒是觉得 你这么想大错特错
I think you have this whole thing upside down.
我是说 听起来你为了那个姑娘
I mean, it sounds like you've bent
鞍前马后的
over backwards for this girl.
可她又为你做了什么
But what has she given you back?
我说了啊 是她允许了我那样的快乐
I told you, she allowed me to be happy
如果没有她 这儿就是人间地狱
In a part of the world that is otherwise a living hell.
允许 哇哦
"Allowed"? Wow.
你竟然用了这个词儿 怂到家了好么
That's kind of fucked up that you would use that word.
你自己是知道的吧
You know that, right?
我只知道 如果没有她
All I know is that there is nothing for me out here.
这儿的一切都不属于我
If I don't have her.
好吧
Well,
那个叫弗依的家伙 貌似是个混球
If this Foy guy is that much of a douche,
如果她有脑子的话 自然会明白的
She'll figure it out if she's smart.
哪个姑娘没经历到过几个混蛋呢
Sometimes a girl has to get a few assholes out of her system
然后她们才会认识到 真正的好男人是啥样的
before she realizes what a good guy looks like.
嗯 也许吧
Mmm. Maybe.
-啊 -你没事儿吧
- Ah! - You okay?
其实这是我第一次抽烟
This is actually my first cigarette ever.
我的天呐
Oh, my God.
-我勒个擦 -响尾蛇
- Oh, shit. - Diamondback.
-是响尾蛇 -日了
- It's a diamondback, yeah. - Fuck.
没事的 一动也别动 它会走开的
It's okay, just hold perfectly still, and it'll go away.
好好好
Okay, okay.
我觉得你不该明天就走
I don't think you should leave tomorrow.
至少过了这星期再走
At least stay through the weekend.
周六不是赶集的日子吗
Isn't the fair on saturday?
赶个毛线 我才不去赶那个破集呢
Oh, fuck that. I'm not going to the stupid fair.
路易丝也会去 还会和弗依一块儿去
Louise is gonna be there, and she's gonna be with Foy.
现在已经够傻逼的了
I don't want to put myself through
我可不能再自取其辱
That kind of fucking aggravation.
那好 我和你一块儿去
Yeah, well, I'll go with you.
让你的前女友看到 你和另一个妹子在一起
No better way to make your ex-girlfriend want you back more
这样让她妒火中烧 再绝没有了
Than to let her see you with another girl.
我不知道
I don't know.
尤其是个性感到爆的妹子
Especially a smoking-hot girl.
当她看到我 我会让她甘拜下风
When she sees me, she'll be intimidated as fuck.
你还挺谦虚的
Oh, you're very modest, I see.
我确实争强好胜 不过我也有两把刷子
I'm a little cocky. But I got great tits.
-喔 -抱歉 抱歉 先生
- Oh! - Sorry. Sorry, sir.
抱歉 老大 抱歉 老爷
Sorry, sir. sorry, sir.
亚利桑那日报
酒吧斗殴 凶手被捕
巴恩斯 快起来 有人来探班
Barnes, wake up. Brought you a visitor.
你个狗娘养的傻逼
You stupid son of a bitch.
你打死的是牧师的儿子
You shot the pastor's son.
你知道他们可能判你绞刑吗
You realize they're probably gonna hang you for this?
谁鸟他们怎么判
Who gives a fuck what they want?
等柯林奇到了镇上
When Clinch gets into town,
他们就无计可施了
it's not gonna matter what they do.
柯林奇会救我出去
He'll bust me out
佛挡杀佛 鬼挡杀鬼
and anyone who tries to stop him is gonna be a dead man.
告诉你 用不了多久
You know, one of these days
就会有人比柯林奇还要快
There's gonna be a man who's faster than Clinch,
还要硬 还要强
and tougher, and stronger.
到时候死的 就该轮到柯林奇了
And then Clinch is gonna be the dead man.
我会叼着雪茄庆祝的
And I'm gonna smoke a fucking cigar to celebrate.
我觉得柯林奇不会喜欢
I don't think Clinch would like
你这么说他的
you talking about him that way.
老婆说老公这种坏话 可不怎么贤惠哟
Not a nice thing for a man's wife to say about her husband.
那好的吧
Yeah, well,
我们拭目以待 你上绞架前
Let's see if he gets here before you
柯林奇会不会来救你
find yourself at the end of the rope.
时间不等人哦
Tick-tock.
哦不不不不不不不
Oh, no, no, no. no, no, no, no!
伙计们 不行不行
Guys, no, no, no.
安德鲁 乔纳森 去去 回家去
Andrew, Jonathan, no. Go, go, go. Go home.
嗨 羊仔
Hey, sheep boy.
嗨
Hey.
天呐 你还好吧 我听说
Jesus, are you okay? I heard about
你的哥哥被关起来了
your brother getting arrested.
我还好 听着 阿尔伯特
Yeah, I'm fine. And listen, Albert.
别担心刘易斯 好吗
Don't worry about Lewis, okay?
他现在这样
Anything that happens to him right
都是他咎由自取 明白吗
now is his own fault, got it?
你都这么说了 当然
Yeah. Whatever you say, sure.
好 我们去集市开开心吧 你知道我最想干什么吗
Good. Let's hit this fair, because you know what I wanna do?
在四十度高温下吃辣食
Eat hot food in 100-degree weather?
不是 我想拍张照片 我从来没拍过
No, get my picture taken. I've never done it before.
-真是马粪啊 -不 我说真的
- That's horse shit. - No, it's the truth.
-不 真的是马粪啊 -呜哦 还真的有坨马粪
- No, that's horse shit. - Whoa! Oh, that is horse shit.
好 好的
Okay. All right.
欢迎光临乡村集市
照相
闪电和上帝创造的奇迹
好了 所有人都别乱动
Okay, everybody hold still!
好像说 德州有个家伙
You know, supposedly, there's some guy in Texas
在拍照片的时候还真的笑了
Who smiled one time while he was getting his picture taken.
不勒个是吧 你没骗人吧
Shut the fuck up. Are you serious?
我们上星期还在说呢 是真的吗
We were just talking about that last week. Is that true?
我也不知道 我也是哪里听来的
I don't know. I mean, I heard it somewhere.
我也不知道真假
I don't know if it's true.
好吧 听起来像是
Yeah, it sounds like the kind of
他们瞎说八道的
bullshit somebody would make up.
好了 所有人都别乱动
Okay. Everybody hold still.
-哦买噶 -我勒个去啊
- Oh, my God! - Holy shit!
不许动
Hold still!
天呐 这破集市
God! this fucking fair!
每一年 都会有这种事儿
Every year, something like this happens.
每一年 都会出人命
Every year, people die.
-真的假的 -每一年都这样
- Really? - Every year.
去年集市里 发生了两场枪击命案
Last year, there were two gunfights,
一场械斗命案 舞台塌方命案
There was a knife fight, a stage collapsed,
溺水命案 还有印第安人袭击命案
There was a drowning, and the indians attacked.
-天呐 为什么印第安人都这么野蛮 -我不知道
- God, why are the indians always so mad? - I don't know.
我是说 这个国家我们差不多
I mean, we're basically splitting
和他们对半分了
this country 50step right up!
他们太自私了
They're just selfish.
净化血液
调节神经
冯·普卢姆博士
药品商店
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen!
来瞧一瞧 来看一看
Step right up, step right up!
来尝一口
Try a sample of...
这位先生 这位女士
Sir and madam, may I divert your attention
我可以占用你们一点宝贵的时间吗
over here just for a moment?
欢迎欢迎 让我为您介绍一种神奇的药水吧
Welcome, welcome. Can I interest you in a miracle cure?
这是我从异域远道带来的
I have only the finest healing tonics and elixirs
包治百病的药 还有长生不老药
procured from the farthest corners of the globe.
奥格登城著名胃药
"Ogden's celebrated stomach bitters."
我能问一句 著了谁的名
Can I just ask, celebrated by who?
谁说过这个胃药好用的
Who's celebrating about stomach bitters?
天呐 看看配方
God. Look at the ingredients.
可卡因 酒精 吗啡 水银外加粉笔
"Cocaine, alcohol, morphine, mercury with chalk."
水银外加粉笔 特么的是神马
What the hell is "mercury with chalk"?
这是科学
Science!
还有红色的法兰绒
And "red flannel."
红色的法兰绒 里面真的塞了件衬衫吗
Red flannel? there's shirt in here?
一小块衬衫布
Pieces of shirt.
好吧 多谢你了内
Okay, thank you very much.
你们想试试吗
Would you like to try?
-哦买噶 -什么
- Oh, my God. - What?
他们来了 他们来了
That's them. That's them.
快 假装你刚说了搞笑的事儿
Quick, pretend you just said something funny to me.
哦我的天呐 你真的 太搞笑啦
Oh, my God! You are... you are so hilarious!
你怎么想出来的 拜托
Where do you come up... no, shit!
你快假装说了搞笑的事儿
You pretend I said something funny.
阿尔伯特 停 停
Albert, stop. stop.
向他们介绍我就可以 快来
Just introduce me. Come on.
我可不会介绍你
I'm not gonna introduce you...
-哦 嗨 -嘿
- Oh, hi! - Hey.
呃 弗依 还有路易丝 对吗
Uh, Foy and Louise, right?
-嗯哼 -正是在下
- Mmm-hmm. - That's right.
这位是安娜 她是
Uh, this is Anna. She's...
-我是他女朋友 -她是我女朋友
- I'm his girlfriend. - She's my girlfriend.
-嗯哼 -她是我的新女票 很爽哦
- Mmm-hmm. - She's the new gf. Big time.
各种嘿咻嘿咻
A lot of sexual activity.
根本停不下来 我都想呆在她身体里不出来
All the time. I live inside her.
所以如果你们想给我写信
So, if you want to send me a letter,
别忘了收信地址写她的私处
You gotta address it care of her vagina.
对
Yep.
你的裙子我也有
I have that skirt.
-哦是嘛 -嗯哼
- Oh, you do? - Mmm-hmm.
我穿着去赶集的 不过是两年前了
Yeah, I wore it to the fair, like, two years ago.
不过这年代你还穿出来了 精神可嘉
But good for you for trying to bring it back.
是啊 我发现只有大笨蛋才会
Well, I figure only a complete idiot
扔掉绝无仅有的好东西
Would throw away a perfectly good thing.
我们要去那边射击游戏场玩
We were gonna go check out the shooting gallery over there.
-你们二位有兴趣吗 -啥
- You guys wanna join? - What?
是啊 一定很有趣 对吧
Yeah, it'd be fun, right?
当然 我们玩点儿带感的吧
Oh, yes, and let's make things interesting.
五美分赌一枪
A nickel a target.
那什么 其实我有点扛不住的说
You know, that's actually, uh, a little rich for my blood.
一美分怎么样
Uh, how about a penny?
怎么回事 阿尔伯特 最近羊毛生意不行吗
What's the matter, Albert? Is business... bad?
那就一美分好了
No, no. a penny it is.
（Sheepskate形似Cheapskate：吝啬鬼）
老天呐 阿尔伯特 你还真是吝啬呀
Good lord, Albert, you're such a "sheepskate." oh!
哇哦
Wow!
哦
Oh...
我们走 路易丝 你可以帮我剪毛
Let's go, Louise. You can "shear" me on.
噢 我又伤到某人了
Oh, no, I didn't!
-你太幽默了宝贝儿 -谢谢
- You're so funny, baby. - Thank you.
可以走了吗
Shall we?
加油
Come on.
等等
Wait, wait, no, no.
拿着 我的好伙计
There you are, my good man.
随时效劳
Indeed.
哇哦 不带这么种族歧视的吧
Oh, wow. That seems unnecessary.
黑奴快跑
用鸭子兔子什么的有啥不好
What's wrong with ducks or rabbits or something?
嗯哼
Mmm-hmm.
六发六中 神枪手啊
Six shots, six hits. Quite the marksman!
礼品给你 女士
There you go, ma'am.
谢谢你 宝贝儿
Thank you, baby.
你想试试吗
Care to try?
你能行的
You got it.
调整呼吸
Just breathe.
看来你欠我六美分 放羊的
Seems you owe me six cents, sheep herder.
好了好了 我知道
Yeah, yeah, I know.
上帝啊
Jesus.
等一下
Wait. hang on a sec.
你想玩点带感的
You wanna make this interesting?
如果我代表阿尔伯特六发六中的话
If I can shoot six out of six on
你就欠我一美元
Albert's behalf, you owe me a dollar.
如果我没做到
If I can't,
-那他就欠你一美元 -你说啥
- he owes you a dollar. - Wait, what?
-一美元 -我从没见过一美元
- A dollar? - I've never seen a dollar.
没人会有一美元的吧
Nobody's got a dollar!
我们要看一美元
Let us see the dollar!
好吧 还真带感
Well, this is interesting.
可以 你要给力哦 咩咩女士
All right. Do your best, ma'am.
这玩意儿有多快
How fast can this thing go?
有两倍速和三倍速
Oh, you can play double or triple speeds,
不过那是专业级的
but that's for the experts
能多快就多快
As fast as you can.
我勒个去
Holy shit!
恭喜
Congratulations!
你赢啦
You're a winner!
谢谢
Thank you.
来吧 你欠他一美元
Come on, you owe him a dollar.
那就是一美元
There it is!
太赞了
It's beautiful!
快脱帽小子 那可是一美元钞票
Take your hat off, boy. That's a dollar bill!
好吧 堂堂一个男人 要让女朋友帮忙射
Well, a man whose girlfriend does his shooting for him.
真想对你说 你还好咓
Isn't that a fine how-do-you-do?
我说 真想对他说 你还好咓
I said, "isn't that a fine how-do-you-do?"
哪里好笑了 笑点在哪儿
How is that funny? What's funny about that?
你还好咓 是打招呼的话 哪里好笑了
"how do you do" is a greeting. Why is that funny?
你 你在笑什么
You, why are you laughing?
我不知道 他也在笑
I don't know. He was laughing.
看来你的前男友没什么幽默感
It seems your ex-boyfriend doesn't have a sense of humor.
你甩了他也是有道理的
I can see why you dumped him.
嘿
Hey!
你给我注意说话的态度 混球
You wanna back up that attitude, asshole?
你开玩笑吧
Oh, you are kidding.
我这辈子都没像现在这么严肃 你和我 决斗
Never been more serious in my life. You and me, pistols.
没人会帮你祈祷的 小子
You wouldn't have a prayer, kiddo.
明早八点整
Tomorrow 8:00 a.m., sharp.
好吧 接受挑战
All right, challenge accepted!
哦糟糕 明天我不行
Oh, gosh. Tomorrow is bad for me,
而且我真的很想到场
And I really wanna be there.
要不我们就定在一周之后的今天吧
Why don't we say a week from today?
那样可以的吧 阿尔伯特
That works for you, right, Albert?
对对 可以 一周之后
Yeah, yeah, that's fine. A week from today.
我明天要处理下我的羊们
I got sheep stuff I gotta do tomorrow, anyway.
一周
One week.
我们走 路易丝
Come on, Louise.
我们去买黄油糖花吃
I'll buy you some sugared butter shavings.
我勒个去
Oh, shit!
哇哦
Wow.
我刚刚都特么干了些什么
What the fuck did I just do?
你刚刚向弗依提出了射击决斗
You just challenged Foy to a gunfight.
刚发生的事 我一点也记不得了
I have no idea what just happened.
我就好像 灵魂出窍了一样
I was, like, out of my body.
阿尔伯特 你看到路易丝脸上的表情了吗
Albert, did you see the look on Louise's face?
没有 咋啦
No. why?
她两眼放光 被你迷到了
She was aroused. She was impressed.
你胸口像着火了一样 荡气回肠啊哥们儿
You had a fire in your belly for a second there, pal.
但你从没让她看到你的这一面
Bet you never showed her that side before.
对啊 我从来就没有这一面过
Yeah, I don't have that side to me.
老实讲我压根不知道刚发生了什么
I honestly don't know what just happened.
阿尔伯特 你惊艳到她了
Albert, you got her attention.
如果你单挑赢了
You beat this guy at a gunfight,
我保证她会后悔甩了你
I bet she thinks twice about dumping you.
安娜 我不能去参加决斗
Anna, I can't be in a gunfight.
我算哪根葱 以为我是柯林奇·莱瑟伍德吗
What am I, Clinch Leatherwood here?
-我会被宰了的 -呜哦
- I'll get killed! - Whoa!
你为什么说这种话
Why would you say that?
因为他是边境最危险的杀手
Because he's the most vicious gunfighter in the territory,
而我可不是
which I am not!
对 你不是柯林奇·莱瑟伍德
No, you're not Clinch Leatherwood.
你肯定会没事的 阿尔伯特
You're gonna be okay, Albert.
我帮你争取到的这一周
That week I just bought you is enough
足够我教你学会射击了
time for me to teach you how to shoot.
你会没事儿的
You'll be fine.
哦对 说起来 还有件事儿
Oh, yeah, by the way, that's another thing.
你特么是哪里学来的神枪法
How the fuck can you shoot like that?
你到底是谁
Who the hell are you?
我老爸是造枪的
My father was a gun maker. I could
我会走路之前就学会射击了
shoot a gun before I can walk.
无所谓了 我胃里恶心 肚子像打了结
Whatever. I'm sick to my stomach. my stomach is in knots.
你太激动了 仅此而已 我们去喝点东西
You're worked up, that's what it is. let's get a drink.
走着
Come on.
嗨 那不是我们的甜心俩口子吗
Hey! It's our sweet young couple.
让我为你们介绍一种纯天然精油吧
Could I interest you folks in some wildroot cream-oil?
集市上总得有人死
People die at the fair.
好了 把你右手拇指
Okay, so you're gonna take your right thumb,
朝向左边
put it all the way to the left.
绕过来 紧紧握住那儿
Cross it over, cradle it right in there,
然后伸直手臂
and then just extend it straight through your...
-这样吗 -手臂伸直
- Like that? - Straight.
哇哦 你从来没玩儿过枪
Wow, you've never fired a gun before.
是没有 不过我有把枪
I... I have not. I own a gun.
对了 在射击游戏场上玩过
No, I fired a gun at the shooting gallery.
好吧 可那种枪是小火力的 这把可是真枪实弹
Yeah, but those were quarter loads. these are full loads.
好吧好吧 准备好哟
Okay, all right, get ready. I'm about
我要用真枪实弹 来射你那些瓶瓶罐罐了
to shoot a full load at your cans.
闭嘴 好好射
Shut the fuck up and focus.
好吧好吧
All right. Okay.
根本不行啊
This is never gonna work.
-不行不行 -你行的
- This is not working. - It's gonna work.
你能做到的
It's gonna work and Louise is
路易丝也会重回你的怀抱
gonna come running back to you.
这玩意儿怎么搞出来
How the hell do you get these things out?
怎么撸都撸不粗来
I'm sitting there jerking that thing off.
嘿 你为什么对我这么好
Hey, why are you being so nice to me?
啥意思
What do you mean?
我是说 你不知不觉就出现了
Well, I mean, you show up out of nowhere.
在这乱糟糟的西部边疆
You're this complete anomaly in my
你完全是反常的存在
world of terriblness out here.
你完全可以去做更牛逼的事儿
I mean, you must have a million
而不是在这陪我这种渣渣
better things to do than this.
咋了 我就不能结交新盆友咩
What, I can't make a new friend?
我看你迫切需要我这种朋友呢
You sure look like you could use one.
也许吧 我就觉得
I guess. I mean, I just... I just
我一点点都不了解你
don't know anything about you.
好吧 我能问个关于你的问题吗
Well, can I ask you something about you?
当然
Yeah, sure.
路易丝有啥好的
Why do you love Louise?
萝卜青菜各有所爱吧
I mean, take your pick. She's...
和她在一起 我感觉超棒
I feel great when I'm with her.
她很优雅 很有趣 永远那么光彩夺目
She's classy, she's fun, she's insanely gorgeous.
嘿听着 她确实很漂亮 没错
Hey, no. Look, she's really pretty, yes.
可老实讲 抱歉我要说实话
But honestly, and I'm sorry to say this,
她除了漂亮 一无是处
I don't see what else she's got going for her.
她给我的印象
My impression was that she was a
就是惹人厌 还自以为是
little sour and self-absorbed,
对于你这么好的一个人
and for a guy with so much going for him,
我就觉得也许你
I just thought that maybe you...
我不知道你觉得我哪点好了
I don't know what you think I have going for me, but...
你看你看 你又来了
You see? There you go again,
老这么贬低自己
Just cutting yourself down.
你表现出来的样子
You act like this girl was performing
就好像这姑娘和你在一起 是一种施舍
some kind of a charitable act by dating you.
阿尔伯特 你其实棒棒哒
Albert, you're a catch.
你那么贴心 幽默 其实还很聪明
You're sweet, you're funny, you're smart.
在这种鬼地方 你完好地活了下来
You've made something of yourself out here.
你知道么 没人会跟你这么说
You know, a lot of people can't say that.
你是个棒棒的牧羊人
You're a good sheep farmer.
哦买噶 拜托好吗 我对放羊狗屁不通
Oh, my God, please. I suck at sheep.
路易丝说得对 我连羊都放不好
Louise was right. I can't keep track of them.
上星期都有羊跑到妓院去了
There was a sheep in the whorehouse last week.
-真的假的 -真的
- Really? - Yeah.
不知咋进去的 然后当我进去找到它时
Wandered in there, and then when I went to pick it up.
也不知道怎么回事 它在妓院挣了二十美元
Somehow, it had made $20.
不过内啥 还是要谢谢你为我打气
But, you know, thank you anyway for what you said.
听着 西部确实是个鬼地方
Oh, look, the west fucking sucks,
但这又不是你的错
But the frontier is not your problem.
关键是你自己
It's you.
你需要多点自信 我的盆友
You need a little confidence boost, my friend.
好了瞄准 羊仔
Now, aim up, sheep boy.
-喔 -嘿
- Oh! - Hey!
-这就对了 -看 就是这样
- There we go! - See? There!
好啦 能打中啦
All righty. That's one.
所以我要做的就是
So, all I gotta do is get Foy to let
在弗依拔枪之前 先对他连开十六枪
me shoot 16 times before he shoots.
然后我就赢啦
And then I win!
你能赢的 我保证
You're gonna do great, I promise.
-挺简单啊 -我们可以做到的
- Easy. - We're gonna get there.
哈珀医生的诊所
-嘿嘿 -太棒了
- Hey! - Yes!
噢
Oh!
搞什么鬼 阿尔伯特 不许带朋友回家
God damn it, Albert! No more friends!
你知道吗 今天你超棒
You know, you did great today.
比上星期不要好太多哦
So much better than last week.
所以我要给你个惊喜
And I have a surprise for you.
你赢取了安娜·巴恩斯
You have earned one of Anna Barnes'
超级无敌绝密秘方的饼干奖励
very special super-super-secret cookies.
嗯哼
Mmm-hmm.
-慢着 这到底是什么 -嗯哼
- Wait, what is this? - Mmm-hmm?
里面有大麻 饼干里放了大麻是吗
This is a pot... This is a pot cookie, isn't it?
-确实放了大麻 -不不不
- It's a pot cookie. - No, no, no.
不不 这玩意儿我完全厚不住
No. I don't do well with that stuff at all.
不就是放了点大麻嘛
It's a pot cookie.
我知道 不行 谢谢
Yeah, I know. No, thank you.
那就陪我吃一小口
Just have a little bit with me.
我最怕的死法 就是嗑药过嗨而死
My worst fear is to OD on a recreational drug.
-不 谢了 -这点大麻会过量么
- No, thank you. - On a pot cookie?
上次有人给我吃了这玩意儿之后
The last time somebody gave me one of these.
我居然幻觉牧羊犬和我心有灵犀
I became convinced that prairie dogs could read my mind.
就咬一小口
Just take a little bit.
-那我只吃一小小口 -就一小口
- I'll take a very, very small bite. - Just a small bite.
-一小小口 -就这样
- A very small bite. - That's it.
开玩笑呢吧
Are you kidding me?
没 我极为认真
Nope. Deadly serious.
你看这小口会让我嗨成啥样吧
Let's see what this does.
如果我没嗨到发疯
And if I don't throw myself off this cliff
把自己甩下悬崖 那
during some awful freak-out, then...
就吃一小口 咬这里
Just take that little bit, right there.
完了 这里你碰脏了
Well, now you've touched it.
那咬另一边的 吃吧
Take the other side. There you go.
好啦
There.
现在 我们妥妥儿地等着看日落吧
And now, we just wait for the sun to set.
感觉怪怪的
This is really weird.
我的感觉正常吗
Is it supposed to be like this?
我没嗑过量吧 是吗
You gave me the right amount, right?
你不觉得我嗑太多了吗
You don't think I took too much?
-尽情滴享受这种感觉吧 -这种感觉
- Just ride it out. - This is...
哇哦 今天我的骨头藏好深啊
Wow, my bones are in really deep today.
就好像 我的皮比以往更厚实了
Like, there's a lot more skin than there usually is.
我觉得我的身体变得厚实 可以准备过冬了
I think my body is padding up for the winter,
这可不正常啊 现在又不是冬天
Which is weird, because it's not winter.
可还是一直在变厚实
But there's a lot more there.
哦
Oh...
我咽口水的感觉也不对
There's something wrong with my swallowing.
平常我不是这么咽口水的
This is not how I usually swallow.
哦天呐 安娜 它发现了
Oh, my God, Anna, he knows.
啥啥啥
What, what, what?
它发现我们嗑药了 它发现了
He knows what we're doing, he knows what this is.
它发现我们嗑药了
He knows what this is.
我们不是一伙儿的
I don't wanna... no, I don't wanna join.
I don't wanna join up.
饭点了 你个懒货
Suppertime, you lazy prick.
对你说句话都浪费口水
Goddamn waste of lungs.
谁是懒货呀 警长
Who's lazy now, sheriff?
嗨
Hey.
哇哦
Wow.
你看上去太赞了
You look amazing.
也许还有点不舒服
And maybe a little uncomfortable.
哎哟我去
Oh, shit!
我穿得太过了 是么
I'm totally overdressed, aren't i?
没啊
No.
我从没参加过正儿八经的舞会
I've never done formal before.
时装店的老板娘推荐我买的这套
And the lady at the boutique told me to buy this
居然根本没人这么穿
and no one else is wearing this.
谁管他们
Who cares what...
这些人都是傻逼啊 你看起来美极啦
These are all fuckers. You look fantastic.
我这样子就像是简·奥斯汀吐了我一身
I look like Jane Austen threw up all over me.
根本不像简·奥斯汀吐
You do not look like Jane Austen threw...
没有的事儿 完美无瑕
No, you look absolutely beautiful.
穿着这身 可以正常呼吸的吧
You can breathe in that thing, right?
穿着这身宽松的衣服
There's nothing I like more than
自由自在地呼吸
putting on some loose, baggy clothes,
感觉不能再棒啦
and just being able to relax.
是啊 工作累了一天 穿上这套真是可以松口气了
Yeah, this is an end-of-the-workday outfit you have on.
这让我想起了我的一条裤子
I'm very glad I remembered the six items
要六个部件才能好好滴穿在身上
I somehow require to hold up my pants.
是嘛
Oh, yeah.
内啥 我喜欢你这裙撑
I like your bustle, by the way.
哦对的
Oh, yeah.
这是现代女性最具魅力的时尚宣言
I really love that the most alluring fashion statement
爱死它了
A woman can make today
就是装饰成一个大屁股
is to simulate a fat ass.
果然是装饰成了一个大屁股
That is a simulation of a fat
就像这样
ass, right there.
如果我是黑人
If I was a black guy, this is the
你这招就太绝了
meanest trick you would play on me.
因为我乍一看 会想 天呐快看
Because I'd be like, "oh, my God! Look,
超级大屁股 我的最爱
there's a fat ass, my favorite."
然后我掀起来一看 就大失所望
And then I'd lift it up and I'd be
我勒个去啊 假屁股
like, "oh, shit, it's a big joke!"
对呀对呀 你掀起来一看
I know, exactly, because when you lift it up
下面啥都没有 就一个铁笼子
There's nothing but a metal cage under there.
哇哦
Wow!
你还真打算来这儿放松心情 缓解工作压力了
You are ready to relieve the stress of the day.
那是当然
Completely.
好吧 最少最少 这样度过我人生的最后一晚
Well, at the very least, this will be a good way
也挺不错的 是吗
to spend my last night alive, right?
阿尔伯特
Albert.
什么
What?
你相不相信我
Do you trust me?
我相信你
Yeah, I do.
很好 你会没事的
Good. you're gonna be fine.
如果我认为你会输
If I thought you were gonna lose this gunfight,
那当初我就不会同意你去决斗 好吗
I'd make you call it off. okay?
好吧
Yeah, okay.
相信我
Trust me.
掌声送给我们的詹姆斯帮乐队
Hey, how about it for the James gang?
谢谢大家 嘿嘿
Thank you. Hey, hey, it's great
回到老树桩镇的感觉真好
to be back here in the Old Stump.
今晚有印第安人来吗 你们是怎么弄到票的
Any indians here tonight? How'd you get tickets?
我猜猜哈 买了黄牛票吧
Let me guess. Scalpers.
我跟你们说 乡亲们呐
But I tell ya, folks, this telegraph
最近出了个叫电视机的玩意儿
machine... That thing is nuts.
当然 它的确比驿马送信要快
I mean, sure, it's faster than the pony express.
它可不能把你小鸡鸡的照片送到家里
But what good is it if you can't
有啥牛逼的
send a picture of your dick?
好了 他们要把舞会灯搬上来了
Okay, they're giving me the lantern.
尽情享用野牛肉吧 也希望各位能享受美酒
Enjoy the bison and I hope you're enjoying your drinks
就像我的马 把尿撒到你们酒杯里那样享受
As much as my horse enjoyed making them for you.
现在让我们排成两排 一起来跳甜心群舞
Now, let's all line up for the sweetheart dance.
来 我们上
Come on, let's go.
不不不 我跳舞超烂
No, no, no! I suck at dancing.
没人看你
No one will notice.
怎么会没人看我
How will they not notice?
因为你做什么都很烂
Because you suck at everything.
瞧谁来了
Well, well!
哈罗啊 放羊的
Hello, there, sheepie.
哈罗 弗依 嗨 路易丝
Hello, Foy. Hey, Louise.
嗨 阿尔伯特
Hey, Albert.
明天可是大日子
So, big day tomorrow.
介意来跳最后一段舞么
Care for a last dance?
就和你
With you?
又不是只和我一个
No, not with me.
-我说的是群舞啊 -噢
- I mean, the dance. - Oh!
是的是的 她和我正要上去跳呢
Yeah. No, yeah, no. She and I are gonna dance.
现在 为我们的群舞伴奏献唱的
And now, to serenade us for the sweetheart dance,
是咱们的马库斯·索顿
our very own Marcus Thornton!
吵死了 哥先撤了
Shit crowd.
你准备好跳怪怪的呆呆的传统西部舞了吗
Ready for weird, stiff, traditional frontier dancing?
我擦还真想跳
Fuck, yes.
男士们渴望爱情
You men who long for love
完全没必要伤心
You mustn't all despair
讲个秘密给你听
There's a secret you should know
保你抓住美女心
To capture the hearts of the fair
不用长得帅 不用追得勤
You may not have the looks, you may not have the dash
姑娘们芳心自暗许
But you'll win yourself a girl
只要你有条帅胡须
If you've only got a moustache
帅胡须呀帅胡须
A moustache, a moustache
只要你有条帅胡须
If you've only got a moustache
也许你是乡巴佬
You may be common folk
没有迷人的傲娇
Without a hint of pride
可你不需要做国王
But you needn't be a king
就能娶美女作新娘
To make any maiden a bride
不用多有名 不用多高薪
You may not have the name you may not have the cash
姑娘们芳心自暗许
But you'll make that girl your own
只要你有条帅胡须
If you've only got a moustache
帅胡须呀帅胡须
A moustache, a moustache
只要你有条帅胡须
If you've only got a moustache
也许你大腹便便
You may be big and fat
也许你贼眉鼠脸
Or uglier than sin
姑娘们闭门不见
All the ladies shut you out
你百思不得骑姐
You're wondering how to get in
山人自然有妙计 保你抓住美女心
Well, here is my advice for how to make a splash
姑娘们芳心自暗许
You can have your pick of gals
只要你有条帅胡须
If you've only got a moustache
帅胡须呀帅胡须
A moustache, a moustache
只要你有条帅胡须
If you've only got a moustache
帅胡须呀帅胡须 帅胡须呀帅胡须
A moustache, a moustache, a moustache
大胡须呀厚胡须
Big moustache, thick moustache
我胡须呀你胡须
My moustache, your moustache
一起来呀帅胡须
Say the word, the word "moustache"
帅胡须呀帅胡须
A moustache, a moustache
我们都有帅胡须
Now we both have said "moustache"
帅胡须呀帅胡须
A moustache, a moustache
只要你有条帅胡须
If you've only got a moustache
该死的混蛋
Fucking asshole.
我去偷瓶威士忌来
How about I steal a bottle of
然后咱们离开这儿
whiskey and we get out of here.
好主意
Love that idea.
我去去就来
I'll be right back.
你裤裆开了
Your dick's out.
嗨
Hey.
我和阿尔伯特掰了
So, Albert and I are gonna split,
不过我想想还是过来 祝你明天好运
but I just wanted to come by and wish you luck tomorrow.
谢了
Thank you.
你在射击场上输给了女人
So, I guess it's kind of weird
真是丢人丢到家了哈
knowing that a woman can outshoot you, huh?
如果你不介意的话
If you don't mind,
我想和我的妹子单独待一会儿
my girlfriend and I are enjoying each other's company.
不过你知道还有更丢人的吗
Want to know the real kicker, though?
喝酒我也比你厉害
I can outdrink you, too.
那我可以向你保证 不可能
That, I can assure you, is impossible.
赌五十美分
Fifty cents to the winner.
一
One,
二
Two,
三
Three.
喵了个咪的
Oh, shit!
别难过
Don't feel bad.
女人的生理结构决定了
Alcohol doesn't harmonize well with a
喝酒本来就不是你们的强项
woman's frail constitution anyway.
我想不是
I guess not.
给你吧
Here you go.
拿着这钱 给你妹子买个脑子
You can buy your girlfriend a brain.
你再说一遍
Excuse me?
你傻到家了
You're an idiot.
你本来拥有全世界最好的男人
You have the nicest guy in the world
对你一心一意
throwing himsel at your feet.
你却对这个傻逼投怀送抱
And here you are with this complete asshole.
我和谁在一起 不管你的事
Who I go out with is my own business.
你还是管好你自己吧 贱人
So, why don't you mind your own, bitch?
你长了这么大双眼睛 怎么会瞎成这样
How are you so blind with eyes that big?
祝你们晚上愉快
Enjoy your night.
我眼睛可没这么大
They're not that big.
亲爱的 你长了双中国人的小眼睛
No, my dear, they're practically chinese.
天呐 爱死你了
God, I love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
这酒咋样
How's that?
哦
Ooh.
哇哦
Wow.
-额 -酒烈点好 可以取暖
- Um... - It'll keep us warm, though.
你冷吗
Are you cold?
有点点
A little.
来 穿上
Here, take...
-不不不 我没事 -不 穿上吧
- No, no, no! it's okay. - No, it's fine. here.
这件正装祖传了九十七代了
This has been in my family for 97 generations.
那首神曲 帅胡须 一直在我脑子里单曲循环
I can't get that Goddamn moustache song out of my head.
那你就想想别的曲子
Oh, just think of another song.
臣妾做不到啊 我们大概只听过三首歌
I can't. There's only, like, three songs.
（斯蒂芬·福斯特：美国十九世纪著名作曲家）
那倒是 而且还都是斯蒂芬·福斯特的歌
Oh, that's true. And they're all by Stephen Foster.
对啊
Yeah.
嗯
Mmm.
呃
Um...
嘿 你知道吗 无论明天发生了什么
Hey, you know, whatever happens tomorrow,
我只是 只是想对你道声谢谢
I just... I just want to say thank you.
呃
Uh...
如果没有你 我的枪法和自信 根本不会有这么大长进
I couldn't have gotten this far without you.
也许因为我醉了
And this may be the booze talking,
也许因为你不断为我打气 或者两者都有
or your pep talk, or both.
我觉得明天我能赢
But I think I can do it.
你知道吗 我觉得我可以打败他
You know, I think I can beat him.
好吧 那我这么说吧 你比过去自信多了
Well, I'll tell you this, you sound a lot more confident
不久以前你还胆小如鼠
than that guy who dragged me out
拉着我从酒吧逃出来
of the saloon not too long ago.
不过讽刺的是
You know, it's funny.
即便到了现在
I still feel like I don't know
这么长时间了 我还一点都不了解你
Anything about you after all this time.
我感觉每次我提到这个话题
And I feel like every time I bring
你就会顾左右而言他
it up, you change the subject.
还真的是没啥好说的诶
There really isn't that much to tell.
我的故事和你的也差不太多
My story is a lot like yours, I suppose.
因为跟你说老实话
Because i'll tell you, I hate the
我和你一样 讨厌西部这个鬼地方
west just as much as you do.
真的吗
Do you really?
我有自己讨厌的原因 真的
For my own reasons, but, yeah.
噢 现在我更喜欢你啦
Oh, I like you even more now.
讨厌一样东西的感觉
There is something about connecting over mutual hatred
比喜欢一样东西的感觉 要深刻多了
That's just so much deeper than mutual love.
太对了 是吧
It's true, right?
如果两个人讨厌同一样东西 那感情简直牢不可破
If two people hate the same things, it creates a bond.
憎可移山啊
Hate can move mountains.
对的
Yes.
哦对啦 免得我忘记
Oh, hey, you know what, before I forget.
布里吉特 布里吉特（喜欢站在屋顶的那只羊...）
Hey, Bridget, Bridget.
对 它听得懂 快过来 真乖
Yeah, she knows. Come here. There we go.
好棒啊
Oh, my God.
这是什么
What is this?
算我对你的一份小小谢意
This is just a little something to say thank you.
阿尔伯特
Albert.
不是很贵重啦
It's nothing huge, it's just...
别太激动哦
Okay, don't get too excited.
到底是啥 是啥是啥
What is it? What is it? What is it?
妈妈咪呀
Holy shit.
我知道
I know, right?
-他竟然在笑 -对
- He's smiling. - Yeah.
照片里他竟然在笑
No, in the picture, he's smiling!
很神奇吧
Isn't that amazing?
上星期我从一个
I bought that off a peddler who was
路过镇上的小贩手中买到的
coming through town last week.
-这就是我跟你说过的那个人 -嗯哼
- This is the guy I was telling you about. - Uh-huh.
竟然真有其事
I didn't even know this existed.
-而且明显这个家伙是正常人 -瞎说
- And apparently, he's not insane. - Bullshit!
那个小贩告诉我的
That's what the guy told me.
拍一张照片要三十秒钟
It takes 30 seconds to take a photograph.
这家伙要在照相机前坐着
This guy would have had to sit there
一直微笑 要保持整整三十秒
and smile for 30 sustained seconds.
我懂的 我这辈子还从来没有
I know. I've never been happy for
连续开心整整三十秒过
30 seconds in a row in my life.
没人做到过 在西部这种鬼地方
No one has! It's the fucking west!
他肯定不正常
He's gotta be insane!
鬼才知道
Who the fuck knows?
你真的太贴心了
This is incredibly sweet.
没什么啦
It's nothing. It's...
是我欠你的
I owe you.
从来没有人为我做过这么贴心的事
No one's ever done anything like this for me.
别这样嘛
Oh, come on, now.
谢谢你
Thank you.
呃
Uh...
对不起
I'm sorry.
我不该吻你
I... I shouldn't have done that.
不 你可以
No, it's... it's fine.
你
You...
对我来说 你只是个很好的朋友 仅此而已
You've just been a really good friend to me. That's all.
好吧 我
Yeah. I, um...
很晚了
It's late.
我该送你回家了
Yeah, I should take you home.
谢谢
Oh, thanks.
明天好运 我会来的
Good luck tomorrow. I'm gonna be there.
好
Good.
我走了
Okay.
呃
Um...
晚安
Good night.
这段是美国著名系列电影《回到过去》的桥段
哈罗
Hello?
那是神马
What, uh... What's that?
没什么
Nothing.
只是个天气实验
It's a weather experiment.
哦
Oh.
我勒个去啊
Great scott!
你确定不能取消决斗吗
Are you sure you can't call it off?
当然不能 不然别人都会叫我懦夫的
Of course not. I'd be branded a coward.
宝贝儿 如果你明天去决斗 那你肯定会杀了他的
Baby, if you fight him tomorrow, you will kill him.
当然 这在决斗中是常有的事儿
Yes, that's what happens in a gunfight.
可他不是坏人 弗依
But he's not a bad guy, Foy.
我是说 他确实是个废物
I mean, yeah, he's kind of a loser
身上还总有股羊骚味儿
and he always smells like sheep.
可那也不该死啊
But he doesn't deserve to be shot.
路易丝
Louise!
我决心已定
My decision is final.
现在 开搞吧
Now, do it.
我好累了
Hey, I'm really tired.
路易丝
Louise!
我社会地位高
My social stature is significant.
我重要无比
I'm an important man.
我有家有业
I have my own business.
人们都妒忌我
People envy me.
哦
Ooh...
怎么了
What's wrong?
-弗依 -过会儿再说
- Foy! - Not now!
旅馆
你好 亲爱的
Hello, sweetheart.
安娜在哪儿
Where's Anna?
好了
Well, now,
我没想到你会来 放羊的
I didn't think you'd show, sheepie.
听着 弗依
Yeah, listen, Foy...
哦
Oh...
Oh. oh...
天呐 你拉完了吗
Holy shit. You all... you all done?
我好了
I'm good.
好吧
Okay.
听着 弗依
Listen, Foy,
她是你的了
She's all yours.
路易丝
Louise,
我很在乎你
You know, I really do care about you.
可是 不知怎么回事
But, I don't know, somewhere along the line.
执迷不悟的我 竟然忘记了
I guess I just forgot that a
感情是相互的
relationship is a two way street.
而且最近我才明白
And i've been reminded recently
有个人关心自己 是什么感觉
of what it's like to have somebody care about me.
我喜欢这种感觉
And I like it.
如果你想和一个长毛傻逼
So, if you want to spend the rest of
共度一生的话
your life with a pussy full of hair,
那我祝你幸福 愿上帝保佑你
I say, go with God and best of luck to you.
我突然发现
You know, I just realized that last
刚最后一个笑话我没讲清楚
joke might not have been clear.
我不是说 她有长毛傻逼
I didn't mean that she has a hairy pussy.
我的意思是 弗依胡须很长
I meant that Foy has a moustache,
你懂的 他给她口交的时候
So, you know, he gets hair in her
他会把毛弄进她下面
when he goes down there.
对
Yeah.
我懂的
I got it.
旅馆
安娜
Anna?
-懦夫 -谢谢
- Coward. - Thank you.
她不在
She's not there.
-她一定会没事的 -我不明白
- Well, I'm sure she's okay. - I don't understand.
为这场决斗我们都准备了一星期了
We've been prepping for this gunfight for a week.
她不可能不来的
She wouldn't just not show up.
你觉得 你们俩会嘿咻吗
Hey, do you... do you think you guys are gonna have sex?
额
Uh...
也许吧 到时候再说 我不知道
Maybe, at some point. I don't know.
好吧 你们嘿咻的时候 跟我们说一声
Well, when you do, let us know
因为我们或许可以玩个4P什么的
Because maybe we can make it an all-us-friends thing.
我们可以同进同出什么的
You know, we can all get in sync together, sexually.
-爱德华 我们还不能嘿咻 -对不起
- Edward, we are not having sex. - Sorry.
露斯 开搞
Ruth! Let's fuck!
来啦
Coming!
她就是不肯改变主意
She keeps my head on straight.
柯林奇·莱瑟伍德
Clinch Leatherwood.
这下好了
Great.
看看 这又可能要了我们的命
Look at this. Another thing that can kill us.
我们真该随身带口棺材
We should all just wear coffins as clothes.
嘘
Shh.
这小破镇里 马上就要有人一命呜呼了
Somebody in this wee shithole of a town is going to die.
昨晚 我的手下看到一个男人 亲了我的老婆
One of my boys saw a man kissing my wife last night.
我想知道是谁
I want to know who it was.
不是吧
Oh, man!
有人要死得很惨了
Somebody's gonna get fucked up.
你们看起来都是好镇民
Now, you all seem like good folk.
好镇民是不会夺人所爱的
And good folk know better than to take what isn't theirs.
而这位
And this...
这是我的女人
This is mine.
那好 我再问一次
So, I'm going to ask one more time.
是谁
Who was it?
嗯
Mmm?
谁
Who?
帮我带话给那位仁兄
Now, you make sure he gets this message.
让他明天中午
Either he meets me outside in the
到镇外的大道上来见我
main thoroughfare at noon tomorrow.
不然我会杀掉更多人
Or I start killing more people.
好吗
All right?
阿尔伯特 你要马上离开
Albert, you gotta get out of here.
小的们 那边转弯的地方 有间没人住的茅草屋
Boys, there's an abandoned sod house back around that bend.
我们就把金子藏到那里去
We'll stash the gold there.
本恩 你带着大伙儿去那里安营扎寨
Ben, you take the men and set up camp.
我要和我的老婆 享受二人世界
I need some alone time with my wife.
明白 柯林奇
Got it, Clinch.
小的们 走 快
Let's go, boys. come on!
下马吧
Go on, get down.
到底是谁
Who was it?
哈
Huh?
马克·吐温
Mark Twain.
什么 真的么
What? Is it?
天呐 这种假话你都信
Jesus. How fucking stupid are you?
喔 喔 喔
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
是谁
Who?
我不想问第二次 到底是谁
I'm not gonna ask you again. Who?
好吧 是布雷迪警长
Okay, it's... it's Sheriff Brady.
求求你
But please, please, please, just...
我求你了 别伤害他 好吗
I'm begging you. Don't hurt him, okay?
我们老夫老妻这么多年
After all the lovely years we've been together
你觉得 你撒谎我还看不出来吗
You think I don't know when you're lying?
我没撒谎
I'm not.
普拉格
Plugger.
告诉我是谁
Tell me who it is or plugger gets
否则普拉格脑袋开花
plugged between his pretty eyes.
-拜托 柯林奇 -你觉得我在说笑吗
- Come on, Clinch. - You think I'm joking?
喔 喔 喔 好吧 我说
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Okay, okay, okay.
谁
Who?
他叫阿尔伯特·斯塔克
It's Albert Stark.
阿尔伯特·斯塔克
Albert Stark.
很好
That's better.
我一直有在保养我的手
I've been keeping it nice and soft.
爽滑吧
See?
嗯
Mmm!
想死我了 宝贝儿 噢 我真的想你
I've missed you, baby. Oh, I've missed you a lot.
走得越远 男人就越寂寞
The longer the ride, the lonelier a man gets.
渴望着心上人的爱抚
And he needs the comforting touch
渴望好好滴松筋动骨
of the woman he loves to soothe his tired bones.
现在 我在场
And now, I'm here,
你也在场
you're here,
让我们共行
and we have time to be husband and wife
夫妻之礼吧
the proper way.
嘿 混蛋
Hey, asshole.
该死
Oh, shit.
我可不能让他光屁股躺着
I can't leave him like that.
这样好多啦
That's better.
阿尔伯特
Albert?
Albert!
阿尔伯特 你得马上离开
Albert, you gotta get out of here.
是的 我是要走了
Yeah, that's... That's what I'm doing.
不不不 十万火急
No, no, no. Like, right now.
柯林奇马上要过来了
Clinch is gonna be looking for you.
我马上就走
Yeah, I'm leaving.
去旧金山
Uh, I'm going to San Francisco.
我一星期前就该这么做
Just what I should have done a week ago.
对不起
I'm so sorry.
好吧 我也对不起你
Yeah, well, you know, so am I.
你老爸咋办
What about your dad?
我问他要一起走吗 他说免了
I asked him if he wanted to come, and he said no.
他在山上 准备把自己和老妈埋一起
He's up on the hill, burying himself next to mom.
听着 我不想让你误会我
Look, I never meant to mislead...
好吧 你知道吗 安娜
Okay, you know what, Anna?
别再浪费我的时间了 好吗
Don't even waste my time, okay?
别再浪费我的时间了
Don't even waste my time.
你有成千上万的机会对我说实话
You had a million opportunities to
可你一直在骗我
tell me, and you just fucking lied.
我没骗你
I didn't lie.
那你的行为叫什么
What would you call it?
你是西部边疆最危险杀手的老婆
You're married to the most vicious killer in the territory.
你难道不觉得
You don't think maybe that's
你一开始就该告诉我吗
something you should have told me.
我没有告诉你 因为我想保护你
I didn't tell you because I was trying to protect you.
胡说 你这么做
Oh, bullshit! You were looking
都是为了你自己
out for your own self interests.
因为我喜欢你
And because I liked you.
我不想吓跑你
I didn't want to scare you away.
我从来没想过 我会遇到你这样的人 阿尔伯特
I never thought I'd meet someone like you, Albert.
啥 像我这样从不杀生的人吗
What, somebody who hasn't killed people? Somebody like that?
对哦 我这样的人 真的很难找了
Yeah, that's really hard to find.
所以女人们都扯着嗓子喊
That's why women are always going,
我的上帝呀 从不杀生的人都死光了吗
"Oh, my God. why are all the non-murderers taken?"
嘿 又不是我的错 好吧
Hey. It's not my fault, all right?
我九岁就和他订了娃娃亲
We were married when I was nine.
九岁
Nine?
这种事如何做到的 难道还有仪式吗
How does that even work? Was there a ceremony?
当然有仪式
Yeah, of course there was a...
我父母都在场 还有几个邻居
My parents were there, and a couple of neighbors.
我只是不想孤独终老
I just didn't want to end up like one of those
就像那些十五岁了都还没嫁人的老姑娘一样
15-year-old spinsters, you know?
我真的不知道
You know, I don't even know...
我真的不知道 我为什么会这么震惊
I don't even know why I'm surprised.
我爱上的每个姑娘
Every girl that I ever fall in love
最终都会让我失望
with ends up disappointing me.
而且每一次 我都很震惊
And every time, I'm surprised.
你爱我
You love me?
你知道么 我翻篇了 你可以走了
Oh, you know what? I'm over it. You can go.
好吧 我是撒谎了
All right. I lied, fine.
那我该怎么说 阿尔伯特 告诉我
What was I supposed to say, Albert? Tell me.
难道我该说 你好 我叫安娜
Was I supposed to go, "Oh hi, I'm Anna!
我十岁就和一个杀手嘿咻了
"I've been fucking a killer since I was 10"?
他还等了一年才和你嘿咻 好一个绅士呀
Oh, he waited a year? What a gentleman.
好吧 十岁不到一点 我凑了整
Well, late nine. I rounded it up.
无所谓了 我和他已经结束了
It doesn't matter. I'm done with him.
我把他敲晕 塞了朵菊花在他屁眼里
I knocked him out, and I stuck a daisy in his asshole.
你都干了啥
You what?
为了你 我什么事都做得出来
That's how much you mean to me.
你知道吗
You know,
我心里爱的那个姑娘 也许根本不存在
I loved a girl who doesn't even exist.
安娜不会是你的假名吧
Is your name even Anna? Huh?
你是不是有个可怕的真名 比如格瘟德林
Or is it something terrible, like gwendolyn?
安娜是我的真名 我正是你心里爱的那个姑娘
My name is anna. I'm that same girl you fell in love with.
那就是真正的我
That was the real me.
也许活了这么久 我第一次怀疑
Possibly for the first time in my entire life.
我是不是配不上这么好的男人
I just didn't think I deserved a good guy.
可你知道吗 我配得上
But you know what? I do.
我爱你
I love you.
是柯林奇
It's Clinch.
见鬼
Oh, shit.
后门有条小路 通向山脚
There's a trail out back that leads out to the ridge.
你快走
Go.
-他会杀了你 -安娜 快走吧
- He's gonna kill... - Anna, just go!
阿尔伯特 他总是数到二就开枪
Albert, he always shoots on "two."
伊诺克 乔迪 你们俩看马
Enoch, Jordy, look after the horses.
他不在这儿 柯林奇
He ain't here, Clinch.
他还没走远 没走远
Oh, he's around. he's around.
斯塔克
Stark!
我知道你在附近 斯塔克
I know you're here, Stark!
本恩 去搜茅房 刘易斯 去搜棚屋
Ben, check the outhouse. Lewis, the shed.
刘易斯
Lewis.
这星期会给你时间去妓院的 好么
Sometime this week, yeah?
抱歉 老大
Sorry, boss.
嘿
Hey!
他在那儿 老大
There he goes! Boss!
该死
Shit.
抓住他
Get him!
驾
Hyah!
哈
Ha!
娘的 我们现在怎么办
What in the hell do we do now?
他会回来的
He'll be back.
啊 柯蒂斯 简直惊心动魄 伙计
Ah, Curtis. That was exceptional, buddy.
我跟你说
I tell you,
等我们逃命出去
When we get out of this, I'm
我就给你找几匹马妓 让你爽爽
gonna get you some horse whores.
听起来很棒吧
Sound good?
要什么类型的都可以
Get you whatever you want.
你如果要头牛妓 我都给你找来
Can even get you a cow, if you want one of those.
想和牛嘿咻吗
Want to fuck a cow?
你貌似是一匹性观念很开放的马儿
You seem like a pretty sexually adventurous guy.
好了 你知道怎么生火么
Now, how the fuck do you make a fire?
爱德华 补鞋店
你确定要这么做吗
Are you sure you want to do this?
是的 我百分百确定
Yes, I'm absolutely sure.
哇哦 不敢相信我们居然真要嘿咻了
Wow, I can't believe we're actually gonna have sex.
爱迪 柯林奇·莱瑟伍德在镇上
Eddie, with Clinch Leatherwood in
也许我们明天就没命了
town, we could all die tomorrow.
所以在这种情况下
So, under the circumstances,
我认为上帝会原谅我们的
I think God will forgive us.
好 那我们开始吧
Okay, here we go.
你兴奋吗
Are you excited?
是的 要第一次看女人私处啦
Yeah, this is my first vagina.
你过去从没有看过吗
You've never seen one?
没有 我觉得看之前 我该来点爆米花什么的
No. I feel like I should have a piece of cake or something.
好 准备好了么
Okay, you ready?
-准备好啦 -好
- Yeah. - Okay.
好
Okay.
啥
What?
你疼吗
Are you in pain right now?
你不喜欢吗
You don't like it.
我喜欢
No, I love it!
不过 不过
Yeah, yeah, it's just...
看起来就像是 两片生牛肉里包着一颗鞭炮
It looks like a firecracker wrapped in roast beef.
是啊 里面还有内容的呢
Yeah, but there's more to it.
那只是外面 其实有好几层的
That's just the outside. There's folds.
好啦 我要合上圣经了
Okay! I'm gonna close the Bible now.
爱迪 那里本来就是这个样子的
Eddie, it's supposed to be like that.
真的吗
It is?
你会很爽的
It's gonna feel good.
幸亏看之前我没有吃爆米花
I'm really glad I didn't have that piece of cake.
好啦
Oh, okay.
准备好了吗
Okay, ready?
感觉会很棒哒 你会很喜欢的
This is gonna be good. You're gonna like this.
好啦 放松点
Okay, easy, now.
抱歉
Sorry. This is...
哇哦
Yeah. wow.
好了 是那里吗
Okay, is that...
-这儿 -对
- Right there? - Yeah.
好的 上啦 哇哦
Sure, okay. wow.
我明白啦 很大是吗
Okay, I get it. It's pretty big, right?
对 你的好大
Yeah, you're huge!
不 我是说你
No, I meant you.
-安娜 -露斯 我能进来吗
- Anna! - Ruth, can I come in?
当然
Sure.
柯林奇在外面
Clinch is out there.
他上来了
He's coming up the stairs!
该死
Shit!
今晚我们要爱爱 请别杀我们
Please don't shoot us on sex night.
你我之间有大问题了
You and I have a problem.
该死
Oh, shit.
你们外来人都是大混蛋
Because your people are such huge assholes,
我要烧死你
I am going to light you on fire.
住手
Stop!
你这混蛋
How is it that you, an asshole,
怎么会说我们印第安语
have the power to speak our language.
我是个书呆子混蛋
I am a nerd asshole.
其他的白种人混蛋都不喜欢我
Since the other white assholes do not
所以我只能自己玩儿
like me, I have always kept to myself.
所以 我看了很多书
Therefore, I have read many books,
学了很多种语言 我数学也很棒
know many languages, and am good at math.
那你在这荒郊野外作甚
Why are you out here?
请帮我松个绑 我自然就告诉你
Please untie me, and I will tell you.
既然他会说我们印第安语
Well, he speaks our language, which means
那我们就该相信他
there's no reason not to trust him.
所以我逃上了火车
So I escaped on the train, and the next
然后我就只记得 一醒来就在你们营地了
thing I remember is waking up in your camp.
而且我已经走投无路了
And now I have no idea what to do.
我给你指条明路吧
I will show you the way.
这是神马
What is it?
你的明路
Your path.
这会让我嗨到崩溃的 我知道的
I'll freak out, I know it.
你不会嗨到崩溃 我保证
You won't freak out, I swear.
我对嗑药很敏感
I'm very sensitive to drugs.
你还真是个书呆子
You fuckin' nerd!
书呆子 傻瓜 脓包
Nerd! Dork! Tool!
好吧好吧
Fine!
他喝了整整一碗
He drank the whole bowl!
啥
What?
你竟然把整碗都喝掉了
You drank the whole bowl!
我去 我去啊 会很惨吗
Oh shit! Oh shit! Is that bad?
你喝光了我们整个部落的份量
That was for the entire tribe!
你会嗨到崩溃 可能会过嗨而亡
You're totally gonna freak out and probably die.
出来了 我看到了
It's coming. I see it, I see it.
是个男孩 斯塔克先生
It's a boy, Mr. Stark.
好的吧
All right.
你不想来抱抱你的孩子吗
Well, don't you want to come hold the baby?
滚开
Fuck off.
好了 把你的牙齿放到枕头底下
Now, you put that under your pillow
牙仙会来取走它 还会留给你一美分
And the tooth fairy will leave you a penny.
哪来的什么牙仙 你个蠢驴
There ain't no tooth fairy, idiot!
快把这些马粪清理干净
Now, clean up that horse shit!
学校
同学们 请欢迎我们的毕业典礼嘉宾
Class, please welcome our graduation speaker,
亚伯拉罕·林肯总统
President Abraham Lincoln.
泥们嚎 呆瓜们
Hiya, shmucks!
八十七年前
Four score and seven years ago,
我穷困潦倒
I was broke,
就像你们一样
just like you.
可现在 我成了总统啦
But now, I'm the president
我现在太特么有钱啦
and I'm so fucking rich.
现在我想嗑多少药 就嗑多少
I can have all the licorice I want.
我觉着他不是真的林肯总统
I don't think that's the real president Lincoln.
嗨 路易丝
Hey, Louise!
路易丝 看看我的这辆酷炫自行车
Louise, check out this cool bike I got!
你想和我一起
Hey, you want to go down to the...
惨啦
Oh, shit!
对不起 对不起
No! Sorry! Sorry!
别别别
No, no, no!
站住
Stop!
滚回来
Get back here!
不是吧 又来
Shit, not again.
抓住那狗娘养的
Get that son of a bitch!
你傻到家了
You're an idiot.
你长了这么大双眼睛 怎么会瞎成这样
How can you be so blind with eyes that big?
我眼睛可没这么大
They're not that big.
打扰一下 阿尔伯特
Pardon me, Albert.
伙计们和我 为你准备了一个特别节目
The lads and I have prepared something special for you.
不用长得帅
You may not have the looks
不用追得勤
You may not have the dash
姑娘们芳心自暗许
But you'll win yourself a girl
只要你有条帅胡须
If you've only got a moustache
帅胡须呀帅胡须
A moustache, a moustache
只要你有条帅胡须
If you've only got a moustache
我们是未来的守护神
We are the guardians of the future.
准备好 就进来吧
Enter when ready.
斯塔克
Stark!
你朝那头秃鹰开枪了吗 你踢它蛋蛋了吗
Did you shoot the black condor and kick it in the balls?
是的
Yes.
你怎么会知道
How do you know that?
那证明你内心深处 蕴含着真正的勇气
It means that true courage does indeed lie within you.
如果你相信这种力量
If you can trust its power...
你就能找到你的幸福
Then you may yet find happiness.
谢谢你所做的一切 科奇斯酋长 我欠你一份情
Thank you for everything, Chief Cochise. I am in your debt.
我们族里流传着一句古老的箴言
There is an ancient proverb among my people:
一个人想要追求真正的幸福 有时就只有一条路可走
Sometimes the only way for a man to find true happiness...
那就是 和大伙儿一起嗑药
Is to take drugs in a group.
谢谢你 让我和你们大伙儿一起嗑药
Thank you for letting me take drugs
我知道我该怎么做了
with you. I know what I have to do now.
好了我的宝贝儿
All right, sweetheart.
让我们看看你的小男友 到底在不在乎你
Let's find out if your wee boyfriend gives a shit about you.
他还有
He's got
六分钟的时间
six minutes till noon.
如果他不来
And if he doesn't show,
那他就只能满大街捡你的残骸了
he'll be picking up pieces of you all over the street.
斯塔克
Stark!
瞧瞧谁来了
Oh, look who's here.
放了她 柯林奇
Let her go, Clinch.
好吧 真爱无敌呀 是不是宝贝儿
Well, now, true love conquers all, doesn't it, sweetheart?
放了她
Let her go,
你和我成熟地解决这个问题
And let's you and me just settle this like adults.
刘易斯 本恩
Lewis, Ben.
-抓好这个贱人 -阿尔伯特
- Come and take this whore. - Albert.
别傻了 阿尔伯特 快走
Don't be stupid, Albert! Get out of here!
快走啊
Get out of here!
太晚啦
Too late for that.
他一直都很傻
He's already been stupid.
是不是啊 阿尔伯特
Haven't you, Albert?
竟敢和我老婆搞七捻三
You've been with my wife.
内啥 我们其实还没嘿咻过
Well, we haven't actually done it,
如果这样能让你舒服点的话
If that makes any kind of a difference.
好吧好吧 我有个提议
Okay, look, look, look. Here's my idea, okay?
你是个牛逼人物 对吧
You're a pretty tough guy, yeah?
那就证明一下看看嘛
Why don't you prove it?
决斗 你和我 此时 此地
Gunfight. You and me. Right here. Right now.
看来你还真想找死啊
You really do have a death wish, don't you?
不试一下怎么知道呢
Yeah, I guess you'll have to find that out, huh?
呵呵
Uh-huh.
拔枪
Take out your gun.
瞄准我
Point it at me.
不
No.
真乖
Good boy.
我数到三 一起开枪
Now, we shoot on three.
一
One.
我打了很多年的扑克牌了
I've been playing cards a long time
牌差我是不会轻易下注的 斯塔克
And I would never have bet on that, Stark.
你哪儿学的枪法
Where'd you learn to shoot?
你老婆教的
Your wife.
惨了
Oh, snap!
马勒戈壁的
Holy fuck.
好吧好吧 在我临死前
Okay, look, look, look! Before you kill me,
让不能让我说几句遗言
just grant me a few last words. All right?
有屁快放
Make it quick.
别杀安娜
Let Anna live.
好吗
All right?
别杀她
Let her live.
不是她的错
This is not her fault.
是我去亲她的 她没亲我 好吗
I kissed her, she didn't kiss me, all right?
不是她的错
It's not her fault.
不过她也没说她已经结婚了
I mean, she didn't tell me she was married.
好吧 她也有一点点错
So it's a little bit her fault, I guess.
好吧 确实是这个样子
So, yeah, I guess that's kind of true.
那就朝她胳膊开几枪就行了
So, maybe just shoot her in the arm.
哪儿跟哪儿啊
What the...
最最后
And one more thing.
我的爷爷奶奶是阿拉伯人
Um, my grandparents were Arabic.
所以我要遵守穆斯林的传统
So, I'm required by Muslim tradition
临死之前要背诵一遍伊斯兰超度经文
to recite the Islamic death chant immediately before dying.
只要一小会儿
This will only take a moment.
嘿 咋啦伙计
Hey, what's the matter, Clinch?
身体不舒服吗
You not feeling well?
你还好吧 老大
You okay, boss?
我是怎么了
What's happening to me?
你知道吗 在西部
You know, there are a million
有一百万种死法 柯林奇
ways to die in the west, Clinch.
比如说 饥荒 疾病 决斗
There's, uh, famine, disease, gunfights.
以及 野生动物 比如蛇
And, uh, wild animals. you know, like snakes.
你知道吗 有意思的是
And, you know, the funny thing is,
它们都不需要来咬你
You don't even have to get bitten.
只要你的血液里
All you need is a little bit of the venom
有那么一点点蛇毒
introduced into your bloodstream.
你就死翘翘了
And you're pretty much screwed.
比如说 如果你把响尾蛇的蛇毒
For example, if you drain a certain amount of venom
灌到一个空头的子弹里
from the fangs of a diamondback
你只要被这颗子弹擦到
rattler into a hollow-tip bullet,
你就挂定了
you really only need one shot.
我知道我的枪法很烂
Now, I knew my aim wasn't good enough
打不中你的要害部位
to hit you anywhere important.
但只要我出其不意开一枪
But if I caught you by surprise...
安娜传授我的枪法 打中你还是没问题的
Well, anna taught me just enough to get me in the ballpark.
只要有一丢丢蛇毒 融到你的伤口里
And just a small amount of venom in an open wound
就足够置人于死地了
is enough to kill a man if he's...
阿尔伯特
Albert.
他挂了 你赢了
He's dead. You did it.
噢
Oh.
是的
Yeah.
他听到我说的锦囊妙计了吗
Did he hear all that smart stuff I did?
额
Uh...
没有 我觉得没听到
No. no, I don't think so.
哦
Oh.
好吧 那也不错
Well, it was still good, though.
对 很棒
Yeah, it was great.
我觉得超级棒
I thought it was really good.
不许动
Stop!
阿尔伯特
Albert!
我现在真的性欲高涨
I'm really horny right now.
我们去找个阴暗角落 嘿嘿咻咻吧
Let's go in the shade and fuck.
干得漂亮 羊仔
Well done, sheep boy.
抱歉我杀了你的丈夫
Hey, sorry I killed your husband.
天呐 我们夫妻缘分已尽
Oh, God. That was never gonna work out anyway.
他是卫理公会教徒 而我却是半个犹太人
He's Methodist, I'm half-Jewish.
-不会是真的吧 -不是啦
- Are you? you are? - No!
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God!
-你也不真的是阿拉伯人吧 -不不不
- You're not really Arabic, are you? - No, no, no.
谢天谢地 刚我还想 一枪嘣了我吧
Oh, thank God. because I was like, "Ah, kill me!"
我懂我懂 就好像 天呐不会吧
I know, right? "No! Oh, my God!"
-不 我们是正常人 -阿尔伯特
- No, we're fine. We're okay. - Albert!
嗨 路易丝
Hey, Louise.
嗨 听我说 如果你还
Hey. Listen, if you want to...
如果你还想聊聊 我很愿意
If you want to talk about things, I would like that.
我是说 今晚我可以去你那儿
I mean, I could come by your place, like, later tonight.
你知道吗 路易丝 我也想
You know, uh, Louise, I would,
可我要回家了 我要做一回真正的自己
But I really gotta go home and work on myself.
你杀了柯林奇·莱瑟伍德
So, you killed Clinch Leatherwood,
西部边疆最危险的抢手
The deadliest gunman on the frontier.
我想是的 哈哈
Yeah, I guess I did, huh?
你知道么 也许杀了他还有悬赏奖金可以拿
You know, there's probably gonna be some reward money.
这我倒从来没想过
You know, I didn't think about that.
你打算拿这钱干点啥
What are you gonna do?
谢谢观赏
过来瞧一瞧 过来看一看
Step right up, folks. Step right up!
黑奴快跑
谁想来试一试枪法
Who wants to take a gander at the shooting gallery?
我想玩玩儿
I'll take a shot.
集市上总得有人死
People die at the fair.
搞毛线啊 谁给我找个白种妞儿来
What the fuck? Somebody bring me one of them white women.